<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Teach a Man to Phish	</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/08/15/teach-a-man-to-phish/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/08/15/teach-a-man-to-phish/</link>
	<description>Hello.  I see you.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Tue, 28 Feb 2017 12:33:23 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
			<item>
				<title>
				By: Lechie				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/08/15/teach-a-man-to-phish/comment-page-1/#comment-1626</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lechie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2005 15:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/?p=567#comment-1626</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Seeing as how I havn&#039;t posted here for a long time I&#039;ve decided to make up for that by wasting loads of your space mwwwhahahaha. I get loads of 419s, and one friday I decided to reply to one being as crazy as I could :


Dr. Adamu Benson
Bank Of The North,
Victoria Island Branch,
Lagos, Nigeria.
My Dear Friend,
I am Dr. Adamu Benson, Branch Manager with Bank of
the North, Victoria Island Branch, Lagos, Nigeria.
I have an urgent and very profitable business
proposition for you that should be handled with
extreme confidentiality.
On January 6,1998 a Foreign Oil Consultant and
contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum
Corporation (NNPC) Mr. James Herbert by name made a 
numbered time Fixed Deposit for twelve calendar months
valued at US$38.6M (Thirty Eight Million, Six Hundred
United States Dollars Only) in my branch.
Upon maturity I sent a routine notification in
accordance with the Bank policy to his forwarding
address but got no reply.
After a month we sent a reminder and finally we
discovered from his contract employers the Nigerian
National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) that Mr. James
Herbert died from an automobile accident.
On further investigation, we found out that he died
without making a Will and all attempts to trace his
next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further
investigations and discovered that Mr. James Herbert
did not declare any next of kin or relations in all
his official documents including his Bank Deposit
paperwork in my Bank.
This sum of US$38.6M has been carefully moved out of
my bank to a Security Company in Europe for
safekeeping.
No one will ever come forward to claim it and
according to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 6
years the money will revert to the ownership of the
Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the
fund.
This prompted us to contact you.We will like to front
you as the next of kin of our late client thereby
making you the legal beneficiary of the sum of $38.6
million U.S Dollars that is presently in a Security
Company in Europe. 
I contacted you because it is against our code of
ethics to own and operate foreign accounts and your
assistance would be needed to claim the money in the
Security Company in Europe.
We have unanimously agreed that 25% of the entire sum
would be for you if you agree to take part in this
profitable transaction,70% for me and 2 of my
colleagues while the remaining 5% would be used to pay
back the expenses that may be incurred during the
course of the transaction by both parties after the
fund has been claimed and lodged in your account. 
In the event that you are genuinely interested in the
transaction,the following information would be needed
from you to expedite action.
1) Your Full Name and Address that would be used to
establish you as the next of kin of our late client
thereby making you the legal beneficiary of the fund.
This would ensure that the Security Company in Europe
releases the Consignment/Fund to you. 
2) Your Private Mobile,Telphone and Fax numbers where
you can be reached at all time because this
transaction entails constant communication.
The transaction is 100% risk free as all modalities
has been perfected to ensure the hitch free success of
the transaction.
If you are interested, send the requested information
via email. 
 
I await your response urgently.
Regards,
Dr.Adamu Benson 
NOTICE:REPLY TO THIS EMAIL ADDRESS(dradamu_benson@fastermail.com)

My reply :


Dear Doktor Adamu
I readed with greatest of interest you most secretest offer of free monies, and I must say that I want all the free monies that you must give to me wich I intend to use wholeheartedly to pay for my space rocket project. Indeed it seems like fortuitous fate has brought you entry into my life at this stage, as I want to make space rocket to drill for oil on the moon and it is too muchly like a godly coincidence that I have the rocket technology I downloaded off the internet and you have the oil technology.
I propose that we go into business together and make a company to drill for oil on the moon called &quot; The company that drills for oil on the moon&quot; or maybe &quot;The oil drilling on the moon company &quot; which name do you like best for our company? MY proposition to you is that we make this company and I get to be the boss person in charge and you be my butler, I shall pay you well, and you will have a warm bed and food for your loyal service. If we employ any other people to help us they shall be your butler, so as the company grows you will get more butlers, but you must find them beds and forage for food for them, I msst insist !!!  I wont have any butlers mistreated, so you will be sorely judged on this!!!
Allow me to explain the merits of my business plan to you. Oil is like water only a different colour and more expensive, a fact that we shall use cunningly to our advantage. It is this very expensive that means when we find our oil on the moon we shall sell it to other people for money. I propose two oil charge tariff, we shall make cheap oil and expensive oil. The cheap oil we shall put in barrels and people shall come to the moon to collect it, but the expensive oil we sell we shall build a pipline to earth and the oil shall flow down the pipe under the dubvious forces of gravity. At the earth end of the pipe we have a big tap, and you and I shall guard the tap so no one can steal our moon-oil. My plans for the future are big and I shall not leave you out my faithfull butler, we shall reinvest our moon--oil profits and buy a refinery on the moon, by this means we will be the first ever gas station on the moon and shall have all business of passing space ships needing to refuel and buy snacks and warm drinks. This is a good an secret business plan of infinite future scope, you must not sell this plan to competition or I will be very mad. I am trusting your honesty in this matter of good faith.

So how much free money are you offering to me then? I need at least 60 billion yen for my moon drilling project, and do not think you can afford all of this. Luckily I was also contacted by Miriam Abacha the wife of the late and badly dresseed General Abache who has offered me almost double the miserable paltry amount you have offered me you cheapskate, but I believe if I wait a few more days and get more offeres, we could put all the money together and afford the mobile moon drilling platform. They will have to supply thier own butlers as I dont want you getting distracted from making my every needs. 

Yours in strictest of confidences and highest regards for my new business partner with hightest of hopes for our combined venture that we shall reach for the stars
Your ever loving business partner
Mr. Derek Cheeseyman  FRACS DISPO IQDT bar none.


His reply, with a classic line at the end :) :


Dear Mr. Derek Cheeseyman,

Ok I have heard you but how can reach i reach you because i need to talk with you on phone,This my proposition has procedure we have to secure some documentation from the government in your favour before this funds will be released into your bank account.Moreso,I need to have your banking cordinates where you want this funds to be transfered into.

Please let me have your direct telephone number so that we can talk on your proposal and mine.

Iam very cheap as you said.

Regards,
Pilow Kwamim.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seeing as how I havn&#8217;t posted here for a long time I&#8217;ve decided to make up for that by wasting loads of your space mwwwhahahaha. I get loads of 419s, and one friday I decided to reply to one being as crazy as I could :</p>
<p>Dr. Adamu Benson<br />
Bank Of The North,<br />
Victoria Island Branch,<br />
Lagos, Nigeria.<br />
My Dear Friend,<br />
I am Dr. Adamu Benson, Branch Manager with Bank of<br />
the North, Victoria Island Branch, Lagos, Nigeria.<br />
I have an urgent and very profitable business<br />
proposition for you that should be handled with<br />
extreme confidentiality.<br />
On January 6,1998 a Foreign Oil Consultant and<br />
contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum<br />
Corporation (NNPC) Mr. James Herbert by name made a<br />
numbered time Fixed Deposit for twelve calendar months<br />
valued at US$38.6M (Thirty Eight Million, Six Hundred<br />
United States Dollars Only) in my branch.<br />
Upon maturity I sent a routine notification in<br />
accordance with the Bank policy to his forwarding<br />
address but got no reply.<br />
After a month we sent a reminder and finally we<br />
discovered from his contract employers the Nigerian<br />
National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) that Mr. James<br />
Herbert died from an automobile accident.<br />
On further investigation, we found out that he died<br />
without making a Will and all attempts to trace his<br />
next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further<br />
investigations and discovered that Mr. James Herbert<br />
did not declare any next of kin or relations in all<br />
his official documents including his Bank Deposit<br />
paperwork in my Bank.<br />
This sum of US$38.6M has been carefully moved out of<br />
my bank to a Security Company in Europe for<br />
safekeeping.<br />
No one will ever come forward to claim it and<br />
according to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 6<br />
years the money will revert to the ownership of the<br />
Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the<br />
fund.<br />
This prompted us to contact you.We will like to front<br />
you as the next of kin of our late client thereby<br />
making you the legal beneficiary of the sum of $38.6<br />
million U.S Dollars that is presently in a Security<br />
Company in Europe.<br />
I contacted you because it is against our code of<br />
ethics to own and operate foreign accounts and your<br />
assistance would be needed to claim the money in the<br />
Security Company in Europe.<br />
We have unanimously agreed that 25% of the entire sum<br />
would be for you if you agree to take part in this<br />
profitable transaction,70% for me and 2 of my<br />
colleagues while the remaining 5% would be used to pay<br />
back the expenses that may be incurred during the<br />
course of the transaction by both parties after the<br />
fund has been claimed and lodged in your account.<br />
In the event that you are genuinely interested in the<br />
transaction,the following information would be needed<br />
from you to expedite action.<br />
1) Your Full Name and Address that would be used to<br />
establish you as the next of kin of our late client<br />
thereby making you the legal beneficiary of the fund.<br />
This would ensure that the Security Company in Europe<br />
releases the Consignment/Fund to you.<br />
2) Your Private Mobile,Telphone and Fax numbers where<br />
you can be reached at all time because this<br />
transaction entails constant communication.<br />
The transaction is 100% risk free as all modalities<br />
has been perfected to ensure the hitch free success of<br />
the transaction.<br />
If you are interested, send the requested information<br />
via email. </p>
<p>I await your response urgently.<br />
Regards,<br />
Dr.Adamu Benson<br />
NOTICE:REPLY TO THIS EMAIL ADDRESS(dradamu_benson@fastermail.com)</p>
<p>My reply :</p>
<p>Dear Doktor Adamu<br />
I readed with greatest of interest you most secretest offer of free monies, and I must say that I want all the free monies that you must give to me wich I intend to use wholeheartedly to pay for my space rocket project. Indeed it seems like fortuitous fate has brought you entry into my life at this stage, as I want to make space rocket to drill for oil on the moon and it is too muchly like a godly coincidence that I have the rocket technology I downloaded off the internet and you have the oil technology.<br />
I propose that we go into business together and make a company to drill for oil on the moon called &#8221; The company that drills for oil on the moon&#8221; or maybe &#8220;The oil drilling on the moon company &#8221; which name do you like best for our company? MY proposition to you is that we make this company and I get to be the boss person in charge and you be my butler, I shall pay you well, and you will have a warm bed and food for your loyal service. If we employ any other people to help us they shall be your butler, so as the company grows you will get more butlers, but you must find them beds and forage for food for them, I msst insist !!!  I wont have any butlers mistreated, so you will be sorely judged on this!!!<br />
Allow me to explain the merits of my business plan to you. Oil is like water only a different colour and more expensive, a fact that we shall use cunningly to our advantage. It is this very expensive that means when we find our oil on the moon we shall sell it to other people for money. I propose two oil charge tariff, we shall make cheap oil and expensive oil. The cheap oil we shall put in barrels and people shall come to the moon to collect it, but the expensive oil we sell we shall build a pipline to earth and the oil shall flow down the pipe under the dubvious forces of gravity. At the earth end of the pipe we have a big tap, and you and I shall guard the tap so no one can steal our moon-oil. My plans for the future are big and I shall not leave you out my faithfull butler, we shall reinvest our moon&#8211;oil profits and buy a refinery on the moon, by this means we will be the first ever gas station on the moon and shall have all business of passing space ships needing to refuel and buy snacks and warm drinks. This is a good an secret business plan of infinite future scope, you must not sell this plan to competition or I will be very mad. I am trusting your honesty in this matter of good faith.</p>
<p>So how much free money are you offering to me then? I need at least 60 billion yen for my moon drilling project, and do not think you can afford all of this. Luckily I was also contacted by Miriam Abacha the wife of the late and badly dresseed General Abache who has offered me almost double the miserable paltry amount you have offered me you cheapskate, but I believe if I wait a few more days and get more offeres, we could put all the money together and afford the mobile moon drilling platform. They will have to supply thier own butlers as I dont want you getting distracted from making my every needs. </p>
<p>Yours in strictest of confidences and highest regards for my new business partner with hightest of hopes for our combined venture that we shall reach for the stars<br />
Your ever loving business partner<br />
Mr. Derek Cheeseyman  FRACS DISPO IQDT bar none.</p>
<p>His reply, with a classic line at the end 🙂 :</p>
<p>Dear Mr. Derek Cheeseyman,</p>
<p>Ok I have heard you but how can reach i reach you because i need to talk with you on phone,This my proposition has procedure we have to secure some documentation from the government in your favour before this funds will be released into your bank account.Moreso,I need to have your banking cordinates where you want this funds to be transfered into.</p>
<p>Please let me have your direct telephone number so that we can talk on your proposal and mine.</p>
<p>Iam very cheap as you said.</p>
<p>Regards,<br />
Pilow Kwamim.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
			</channel>
</rss>
