<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>hackers &#8211; AFK Gamer</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/tag/hackers/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/</link>
	<description>Hello.  I see you.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Thu, 07 Aug 2014 11:49:50 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Farmers and Botters and Gnomes</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/07/05/farmers-and-botters-and-gnomes/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/07/05/farmers-and-botters-and-gnomes/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 18:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[farmers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world of warcraft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/07/05/farmers-and-botters-and-gnomes/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve been up to the devil&#8217;s business lately in World of Warcraft &#8212; nothing illegal, sploitish or untoward, I assure you. The whole thing hasn&#8217;t played out yet so I can&#8217;t write out the unseemly details until I get everything &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/07/05/farmers-and-botters-and-gnomes/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve been up to the devil&#8217;s business lately in World of Warcraft &#8212; nothing illegal, sploitish or untoward, I assure you.  The whole thing hasn&#8217;t played out yet so I can&#8217;t write out the unseemly details until I get everything that&#8217;s coming to me.  (That&#8217;s a little teaser.)</p>
<p>Fortunately for me, the WoW forums has provided some entertainment.  </p>
<p>First, amusing and innovative, a gold farming outfit took to the skies to advertise their gold site across several servers:  &#8220;<a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.html?topicId=116362448&#038;postId=1162219024&#038;sid=1">Gold Spam: Going to new heights. Literally</a>&#8221; and &#8220;<a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.html?topicId=116362212&#038;sid=1&#038;pageNo=1">Emerald Dream server just got hacked it seems</a>&#8220;.  Mods and the original posters pulled the screenshots before I could capture (damn them!), but basically, gnomes fell from the skies to their deaths to form the words and web addy for a gold farming site.</p>
<p>From the first post:</p>
<blockquote><p>Server: Skywall<br />
Time: 1 am server<br />
Gold Spam of the Month&#8230;</p>
<p>Level 1 gnome warriors are falling from the sky in Ironforge to their deaths, and instantly releasing leaving their bodies on the ground in Ironforge.</p>
<p>&#8220;Nothing new&#8221; you say? Well, so far the bodies have spelled out < < The Name Of A Site That Will Not Be Mentioned >> and keep falling to form more letters as I type this.</p>
<p>I&#8217;m currently at the noob starting zone for the gnomes, in Dun Morogh, and have been watching lvl 1 gnome warriors being created, &#8220;flying&#8221; 20 feet into the air, then walking towards ironforge. STILL IN THE AIR.</p></blockquote>
<p>Oh the gnomity!</p>
<p><span id="more-1505"></span>Emailer Indy, who never goes on an adventure without a hat, found this interesting &#8211; bound for deletion &#8211; thread: &#8220;<a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.html?topicId=116453087&#038;sid=1&#038;pageNo=1">From the Front Lines (A botter&#8217;s story.)</a>&#8221;  Confessed botter Andeasdr wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Short introduction about myself.</p>
<p>1.) I&#8217;m a bot developer.<br />
2.) I&#8217;m an American.<br />
3.) I work for companies that cheat at WoW for a living.</p>
<p>Purpose of this post? Several reasons.</p>
<p>1.) High five to Blizzard. I botted and cheated at this game for well over a year without a single ban. June ban wave knocked out 8 of my personal accounts (including my epiced out 70 main), and over 200 company accounts. Never thought I&#8217;d see the day that Blizzard would completely devastate the botting community, not only dealing a nearly lethal blow to the most popular, but as well as decimating the less popular alternative program.</p>
<p>2.) Let players know that Blizzard -is- dealing with bots. They may not deal with bots in the way you expect. Reporting bots may at times seem fruitless, but trust me, they are doing their jobs. I&#8217;ve seen complaints on these forums many times, and can think to myself &#8220;If only people knew&#8221;. Blizzard can not delve into what they&#8217;re doing, and you don&#8217;t see much proof of their accomplishments, but they&#8217;re there.</p>
<p>3.) Let players know that Blizzard is keeping up with this. I stopped cheating on personal accounts after the last ban wave, so the second ban wave they did a couple days ago didn&#8217;t hurt me personally (unless you count the wallet). Yes, they&#8217;ve just done two ban waves in the span of 3 weeks. While everyone was trying to recuperate losses, they go and knock the crap out of them once more.</p>
<p>4.) Let players know that the asshat spammers have nothing to do with me. They trip whisper detection and auto-replys so often, it pisses me off too!</p>
<p>5.) Let you know that not all of us want to ruin the game to fill our wallets. I am in this profession because I love Blizzard games, and I&#8217;m good at what I do (and who can argue with playing games for a living&#8230;). Given an oppurtunity to work for Blizzard instead, I&#8217;d do it in a heartbeat. Unfortunately they don&#8217;t pay relocation costs and have no HQ close to where I live, nor do I think I&#8217;m qualified&#8230;being only 21 and having little schooling.</p>
<p>Basically, Blizzard is doing a killer job. Love this game, love the company, and a huge fan.</p>
<p>Blizzard&#8217;s Public Relations isn&#8217;t so hot because they have to keep many things secret, so if this post can help improve yalls image, I&#8217;m willing to endure the flames.</p>
<p>Oh, and I absolutely love the plausible deniability you gave botters a few days ago with the server news. &#8220;Players may experience disconnections or be unable to connect.&#8221;.</p>
<p>Was a good laugh when we realized that everyone getting DCed and Banned could use that as a cover story.</p>
<p>Thanks Blizzard for everything you do, you&#8217;re one of the few companies I actually believe does what they do for the customers. No matter how much some of the outspoken ones whine and complain. </p></blockquote>
<p>The forum websleuths do their best to debunk his claims, but my opinion, he remained un-debunked.  </p>
<p>Someone mentioned the EQ hacks that used to go on which reminded me of that one EQ proggy, had to run on Linux, hell if I can remember the name tho.  What it did was, you would zone in and could see what bosses were up and what loot they had.  Anything Linux and dual boot and I&#8217;m defeated, so lucky for my guild, <strong>we had a guy</strong>.  </p>
<p>So this guy would zone into &#8230; say Sebilis &#8230; and then tell us, &#8220;Nah, you don&#8217;t wanna do Sebilis.  Maybe Howling Stones has something more to your liking.&#8221; and off he&#8217;d go.  He was richer than God and never got caught and I learned an important lesson:  In games, just like in real life, it&#8217;s good to know <strong>A Guy</strong>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/07/05/farmers-and-botters-and-gnomes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>6</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside Their CM Accounts, Wreaking Havocs</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/06/13/inside-their-cm-accounts-wreaking-havocs/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/06/13/inside-their-cm-accounts-wreaking-havocs/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2007 15:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world of warcraft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/06/13/inside-their-cm-accounts-wreaking-havocs/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[In case you missed the keylogging hijinks on the World of Warcraft forums, this epic/legendary/gigantor thread covers the details &#8212; Blizzard Community Managers Nethaera and Drokthul get keylogged, the lucky bastard hackers use the CM accounts to post more keyloggers, &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/06/13/inside-their-cm-accounts-wreaking-havocs/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In case you missed the keylogging hijinks on the World of Warcraft forums, this <a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.html?topicId=109933223">epic/legendary/gigantor thread</a> covers the details &#8212; Blizzard Community Managers Nethaera and Drokthul get keylogged, the lucky bastard hackers use the CM accounts to post more keyloggers, PROFIT!, Blizzard&#8217;s Eyonix saves the day by banning the CM accounts, everyone has a good laugh and hugs it out.</p>
<p>True story.  Except for the hugging.</p>
<p>(Thanks emailer Byron!)</p>
<p>The image links in that thread are probably dead thanks to the 10 million people clicking wildly to see Neth and Drokthul&#8217;s shame.  Here you go:  <a href="http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1412/544090387_52d7846e66_o.jpg">Drokthul</a> and <a href="http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1250/544090385_f535be27bc_o.jpg">Nethaera</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/06/13/inside-their-cm-accounts-wreaking-havocs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nerd Rage</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/04/10/nerd-rage/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/04/10/nerd-rage/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2007 14:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world of warcraft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/04/10/nerd-rage/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Back to our regularly scheduled World of Warcraft programming &#8230; This WoW poster and I agree on this: the WoW forums are the ideal place to seek legal advice. Puddle, level 12 trolling alt of the Shattered Halls realm, wrote &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/04/10/nerd-rage/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back to our regularly scheduled World of Warcraft programming &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.html?topicId=93969926&#038;sid=1&#038;pageNo=1">This WoW poster</a> and I agree on this:  the WoW forums are the ideal place to seek legal advice.</p>
<p>Puddle, level 12 trolling alt of the Shattered Halls realm, wrote in &#8220;Acct hacked and im gonna sue&#8221;:</p>
<blockquote><p>Does anyone have any advice for me a guy hacked my wow acct and it was my bank toon, we lost 100s of hours of play time.</p>
<p>1} Has anyone ever sued a person for hacking there acct</p>
<p>2} should I file the police report first or not</p>
<p>3}I know in the police report there needs to be a fraud charge so they cantt bankrupt out any other helpfull hints</p>
<p>4}we are going after this guy in court if you have any helpfull ideas please post</p></blockquote>
<p>*points to the &#8220;Please Don&#8217;t Feed the Lawyers&#8221; sign.*</p>
<p>(Six sentences and not a one is correct.  Sad.)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/04/10/nerd-rage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Keep It Secret, Keep It Safe</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/11/06/keep-it-secret-keep-it-safe/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/11/06/keep-it-secret-keep-it-safe/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2006 17:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world of warcraft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/11/06/keep-it-secret-keep-it-safe/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Lum&#8217;s been googling for World of Warcraft hacks again. From Gamespot, the down and dirty: The World of Warcraft guild Overrated has been permanently banned by Blizzard Entertainment after it was caught cheating in the massively multiplayer online role-playing game. &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/11/06/keep-it-secret-keep-it-safe/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lum&#8217;s been <a href="http://www.brokentoys.org/2006/11/05/the-walls-have-eyes-but-are-missing-form-and-function/">googling for World of Warcraft hacks</a> again.  From Gamespot, <a href="http://www.gamespot.com/news/6160983.html">the down and dirty</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>The World of Warcraft guild Overrated has been permanently banned by Blizzard Entertainment after it was caught cheating in the massively multiplayer online role-playing game. Guild members used an exploit that essentially knocked down walls, according to postings on World of Warcraft-related forums.</p></blockquote>
<p>i.e. used an exploit that took advantage of client-side movement.</p>
<p>Well fucking duh.  EVERYBODY, including my teenaged gaming neighbor Skippy, knows that WoW has too much in the client.  </p>
<p>This is also a good reminder of a life lesson most of us learned in grade school:  Two people cannot keep a secret.  </p>
<p>And its corollary:  There&#8217;s no way in Hell an entire guild can keep a secret.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/11/06/keep-it-secret-keep-it-safe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>6</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>The August 2006 Warcraft Keylogger Incident</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/09/06/the-august-2006-warcraft-keylogger-incident/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/09/06/the-august-2006-warcraft-keylogger-incident/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2006 12:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Asides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world of warcraft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/09/06/the-august-2006-warcraft-keylogger-incident/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[The official word from the Warcraft forums about The August 2006 Keylogger: &#8220;We would like to warn players of a keylogger scam that is getting posted on the forums. This scam puts fake URLs, or hyperlinks, that once clicked will &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/09/06/the-august-2006-warcraft-keylogger-incident/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.html?topicId=14714952">official word from the Warcraft forums about The August 2006 Keylogger</a>:  &#8220;We would like to warn players of a keylogger scam that is getting posted on the forums. This scam puts fake URLs, or hyperlinks, that once clicked will install a trojan to steal your account name and password. It is important that players take caution when being directed to outside websites and update their security on their computers accordingly. [&#8230;]&#8221;  <a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.html?topicId=14714952&#038;postId=153704407&#038;sid=1#37">Reply #37</a>, by Landragoran of the Draenor realm, summarized the real details (this is what I heard/read also):  &#8220;just for everyone who doesn&#8217;t know, the site currently being used for distribution of this keylogger is tulang1.com (i&#8217;m not going to type out the whole link in fear of someone clicking it and blaming me). basically if you see any link with &#8220;tulang&#8221; in it, do not click the link.  so far i have seen the link in a post claiming that DnT had downed the 4 horsemen, SS&#8217;s inside, and 2 posts with the title &#8220;&#8216;Trial Version&#8217; question&#8221;, wherein someone claims they purchased a computer that came with a trial version of WoW and they want to know if installing it will install the full version but only allow them to play for a short amount of time, or only install part of the game. they then provide a link to the &#8220;trial version&#8221; that they are talking about.&#8221;  (<a href="http://www.furl.net/search?search=cache&#038;id=11613237&#038;url=http%3A%2F%2Fforums.worldofwarcraft.com%2Fthread.html%3FtopicId%3D14714952%26sid%3D1"><del datetime="2009-10-14T03:24:08+00:00">Furl archive of thread, page 1</del></a> &#8212; <em>oh well, Furl&#8217;s dead now, but whatcanyado</em>.)</p>
<p><img src="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/images/afk-end.png" class="noborder" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/09/06/the-august-2006-warcraft-keylogger-incident/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Important Gaming Lesson:  Brothers are Evil</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/08/29/important-gaming-lesson-brothers-are-evil/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/08/29/important-gaming-lesson-brothers-are-evil/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2006 14:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Asides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world of warcraft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/08/29/important-gaming-lesson-brothers-are-evil/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[If we learn anything from gaming, it is this: Brothers are the shittiest humans in the world. It&#8217;s always brothers that are hacking, hijacking, botting, cheating and generally abusing game characters any chance they get. I&#8217;m considering adding the question &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/08/29/important-gaming-lesson-brothers-are-evil/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If we learn anything from gaming, it is this:  Brothers are the shittiest humans in the world.  It&#8217;s always brothers that are hacking, hijacking, botting, cheating and generally abusing game characters any chance they get.  I&#8217;m considering adding the question &#8220;Do you have a brother?&#8221; to our guild application and I&#8217;ll just auto-deny anyone with a male sibling.  I have an older brother myself, true, but I keep a sharp eye on him whenever technology is involved.  Anyways, it appears that brothers are at it again, deleting Warcraft characters across the realms.  Either brothers or a trojan keylogger &#8212; my research is incomplete at this point.  There&#8217;s a few reports this is related to a poser CTmod site and/or a Best Warcraft Video Ever site, players are warned to download mods only from trusted sites and only .zip files rather than executables, bla bla, you know the drill.  I&#8217;ll update this post with a few links when the forums wake up again.  (Maintenance day, donchaknow.)  The smart money is on goddamn brothers, however.  UPDATE:  Here&#8217;s the <a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.html?topicId=14051642&#038;sid=1">Customer Service forum thread</a> seeking additional details from affected account owners.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/08/29/important-gaming-lesson-brothers-are-evil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paladins are Enablers for Hackers</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/07/19/paladins-are-enablers-for-hackers/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/07/19/paladins-are-enablers-for-hackers/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 12:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Asides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pvp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[screenshots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world of warcraft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/07/19/paladins-are-enablers-for-hackers/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I see a level 60 player of the Warcraft Smolderthorn realm who should have checked on his forum post and done a quick edit job, if not a complete deletion: &#8220;@ Malican of Transcendence (hacker)&#8221;. (Archive: Forum thread and screenshot)]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I see a level 60 player of the Warcraft Smolderthorn realm who should have checked on his forum post and done a quick edit job, if not a complete deletion:  <a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.aspx?FN=wow-realm-smolderthorn&#038;T=152882">&#8220;@ Malican of Transcendence (hacker)&#8221;</a>.  (Archive:  <a href="http://www.furl.net/search?search=cache&#038;id=10493983&#038;url=http%3A%2F%2Fforums.worldofwarcraft.com%2Fthread.aspx%3FFN%3Dwow-realm-smolderthorn%26T%3D152882">Forum thread</a> and <a href="http://www.furl.net/search?search=cache&#038;id=10493961&#038;url=http%3A%2F%2Fimg132.imageshack.us%2Fmy.php%3Fimage%3Dwowmalicanhack9zo.gif">screenshot</a>)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/07/19/paladins-are-enablers-for-hackers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>30 Million Warcraft Gold GONE!</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/06/10/30-million-warcraft-gold-gone/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/06/10/30-million-warcraft-gold-gone/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 11:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[farmers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virtual currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[warcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world of warcraft]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/06/10/30-million-warcraft-gold-gone/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[They tried to sneak this one past me with a late Friday afternoon post on the Warcraft front page: World of Warcraft accounts closed! There was no need to sneak &#8212; not like I&#8217;m getting rich in this game, or &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/06/10/30-million-warcraft-gold-gone/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>They tried to sneak this one past me with a late Friday afternoon post on the Warcraft front page:  <a href="http://forums.worldofwarcraft.com/thread.aspx?fn=wow-general&#038;t=8653370">World of Warcraft accounts closed</a>!  There was no need to sneak &#8212; not like I&#8217;m getting rich in this game, or off of this game.</p>
<p>Ordinn, Blizzard economist wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>In keeping with Blizzard&#8217;s aggressive stance against cheating in World of Warcraft, we banned over 30,000 accounts in the month of May, and with that removed well over 30 million gold from the economy across all realms. The banned accounts were taking part in activities that violate the game&#8217;s Terms of Use, including using third-party programs to farm gold and items, which severely impacts the economy of a realm and the overall game enjoyment for all players.</p>
<p>We will continue to aggressively monitor all World of Warcraft realms in order to protect the service and its players from the harmful effects of cheating. Please note that selling World of Warcraft content, such as gold, items, and characters, can result in a permanent ban of the involved accounts from World of Warcraft.</p>
<p>Many account closures come as the direct result of tips reported to our GMs in game or emailed to hacks@blizzard.com by legitimate World of Warcraft players. If you suspect that a World of Warcraft player is using an illegal third-party program to farm gold or items, or is otherwise violating our Terms of Use, please report the suspected infraction via one of the means listed above. All reports will be investigated, and those that prove false will not result in corrective action.</p>
<p>Thank you for your continued support, and good luck with your adventures in Azeroth!</p></blockquote>
<p>I&#8217;d like to imagine that this was one huge sting, set up over the past few weeks, involving undercover GM agents and late night interrogations of suspected farmers.  Probably it was far less glamorous:  players ratting out some guys who were stealing spawns in Eastern Plaguelands.</p>
<p>One of our guild priests is relieved he bought his epic mount last week instead of waiting &#8212; supply and demand being what they are.  And when I say &#8220;bought&#8221;, you know I meant he used some real life scratch to IGE the damn thing because who has the energy to farm 1000 gold for their second, third or fourth level 60?  Nobody I know.</p>
<p><small>(<a href="http://www.furl.net/search?search=cache&#038;id=9134852&#038;url=http%3A%2F%2Fforums.worldofwarcraft.com%2Fthread.aspx%3Ffn%3Dwow-general%26t%3D8653370">Furl archive of forum announcement</a>)</small></p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/06/10/30-million-warcraft-gold-gone/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>6</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>EQdkp Under Attack!</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/05/09/eqdkp-under-attack/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/05/09/eqdkp-under-attack/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2006 19:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Asides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[guilds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[screenshots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/05/09/eqdkp-under-attack/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[If your guild, like mine, is using the venerable EQdkp program to track guild raid points, attendance and the like, it&#8217;s time to patch a security fix. (DO IT NOW!) &#8220;A security vulnerability was recently discovered in all current versions &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/05/09/eqdkp-under-attack/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If your guild, like mine, is using the venerable <a href="http://eqdkp.com/">EQdkp</a> program to track guild raid points, attendance and the like, it&#8217;s time to patch a security fix.  (DO IT NOW!)  &#8220;A security vulnerability was recently discovered in all current versions of EQdkp that could allow remote code inclusion on specific server configurations, if register_globals is enabled.&#8221;  More discussion is available <a href="http://forums.eqdkp.com/index.php?s=&#038;act=ST&#038;f=1&#038;t=4684">here</a> in a forum thread.  You&#8217;re probably wondering how in the world did I run across this rather obscure gaming news?  Is the AFK Gamer staff so on top of late-breaking news that nothing escapes their notice?  Thank you.  Actually, my guild&#8217;s DKP site got whacked last night, although we didn&#8217;t discover it until the guildmates started checking their up-to-the-minute DKP balances at work (as you do) and were greeted with this <a href="http://static.flickr.com/49/143577912_fe98fd11f8_o.png">defacement</a> (Flickr screenshot), which, loosely translated means &#8230; I cut off your American head and drink soup out of the skull.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/05/09/eqdkp-under-attack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lineage Identity Thefts</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/21/lineage-identity-thefts/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/21/lineage-identity-thefts/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2006 13:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Asides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[farmers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lineage]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/21/lineage-identity-thefts/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Approximately 220,000 Lineage accounts were created with stolen identities on the South Korean servers. The prime suspects? Chinese gamers and farmers. (Of course.) Read: Identity theft feeds $1bn gaming black market. The South Korean gamers aren&#8217;t taking that shit lying &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/21/lineage-identity-thefts/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Approximately 220,000 Lineage accounts were created with stolen identities on the South Korean servers.  The prime suspects?  Chinese gamers and farmers.  (Of course.)  Read: <a href="http://www.vnunet.com/vnunet/news/2150677/identity-theft-online-games">Identity theft feeds $1bn gaming black market</a>.  The South Korean gamers aren&#8217;t taking that shit lying down and are slaughtering the Chinese gamers in retaliation.  Read:  <a href="http://news.ft.com/cms/s/ba7904ca-a27e-11da-9096-0000779e2340.html">South Korean gamers stage online massacre of Chinese</a>.  I know what you&#8217;re thinking:  how long until this scam arrives in other games with huge farmer operations?  I dunno, maybe it&#8217;s already here.  (dun dun DUN!)  (More to read:  The AP report, <a href="http://www.post-gazette.com/pg/06052/658467.stm">In South Korea, an online game led to identity theft</a>.)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/21/lineage-identity-thefts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
