<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bio &#8211; AFK Gamer</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/category/bio/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/</link>
	<description>Hello.  I see you.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Thu, 07 Aug 2014 11:49:50 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Construction Zone Ahead</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/10/03/construction-zone-ahead/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov -0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/10/03/construction-zone-ahead/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Changes coming to this corner of blogdom: 1. A redirect to Foton&#8217;s own domain. I&#8217;m all about autonomy. 2. World of Warcraft and EQ2 diaries. With SWG just about dead and buried, not much hap in Gamma Gaming&#8217;s online life. &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/10/03/construction-zone-ahead/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Changes coming to this corner of blogdom:</p>
<p>1.  A redirect to Foton&#8217;s own domain.  I&#8217;m all about autonomy.</p>
<p>2.  World of Warcraft and EQ2 diaries.  With SWG just about dead and buried, not much hap in Gamma Gaming&#8217;s online life.  In a few weeks, that&#8217;s all about to change.  New windmills to joust, more assclowns to defeat in a battle of wits.  Don&#8217;t miss it.</p>
<p>ETA on redirect:  week of 10/3/04<br />ETA on WoW &#038; EQ2:  they &#8220;say&#8221; 11/15/04 &#8230; I say, someone is going to blink first.  But mid-fall is a good estimate.<span class="shortpost"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cyber Sex, Lies and The Beatles</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/09/11/cyber-sex-lies-and-the-beatles/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov -0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[I, Moral Barometer]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/09/11/cyber-sex-lies-and-the-beatles/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m like Dennis Miller. I can toss out obscure references and assume that The Intelligent will catch them. Anyhow, today, while waiting for a MMOG release to save me, I was watching Court TV and caught some hosebag&#8217;s testimony &#8230; &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/09/11/cyber-sex-lies-and-the-beatles/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m like Dennis Miller.  I can toss out obscure references and assume that The Intelligent will catch them.</p>
<p>Anyhow, today, while waiting for a MMOG release to save me, I was watching Court TV and caught some hosebag&#8217;s testimony &#8230; let me summarize for the cheap seats, <span id="more-3"></span>this mom puts a few bullets in this assbag&#8217;s body after she finds him jacking off in bed while watching porn &#8230; o ya, her three year old daughter is in the bed with him, also naked.<span class="fullpost"></p>
<p>Do we really need to waste government dollars prosecuting this shit?  He&#8217;s a confirmed drug dealer, jacking off in bed to porn with his live-in girlfriend&#8217;s three year old daughter, also naked, in bed next to him.  And there&#8217;s some question about this?  There is someone on earth mourning this fuck&#8217;s death?</p>
<p>Back to the hosebag testifying on the assbag&#8217;s behalf.  Hosebag was high 40 percent of the time (her words) and yet (and YET!), whether she&#8217;s straight OR high, she has the same clarity &#8230; even when smoking 8-balls.  I don&#8217;t even know what the fuck an 8-ball is, but it sounds expensive, as it involves solid cocaine (which I learned from the witness).</p>
<p>Yes, she delivered this testimony with a straight face and yes, the Court TV anchor team agrees that she is a VERY credible witness because she can be so blunt and honest about her fucked-up lifestyle.  (Oops, did I forget to mention that the hosebag is the GODDAMN BABYSITTER?)</p>
<p>This doesn&#8217;t really have to do with the State of MMOGs Today, other than, while I was pondering the sorry state that I&#8217;m in because I need something to go gold to give me hope &#8230; I realized that I may be taking Crazy Pills here.  </p>
<p>Am I the only one that thinks hosebags should go away before they can be sworn in? &#8230; and, certainly, anchor teams should understand that hosebags can&#8217;t possibly be credible witnesses.  For fuck&#8217;s sake, listening to her was like reading a Hollywood treatment for <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0086250/">Scarface</a> II.</p>
<p>O ya, and I flashbacked (in a &#8220;I haven&#8217;t really spent significant time being high and for sure not around children&#8221; way) on this hosebag when I read the latest <a href="http://forums.station.sony.com/swg/board/message?board.id=artisan&#038;message.id=44114#M44114">Happy Happy Joy Joy Star Wars shit</a>.</p>
<p>[Hints:  Cyber (online) Sex (jacking off), Lies (anything SOE tells you), and the Beatles (happiness is a warm gun, bang bang, shoot shoot)]</p>
<p>Back away from the 8-balls &#8230; whatever those are, they sound bad.</span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>About Foton</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/06/13/about-foton/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2004 13:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/06/13/about-foton/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[A dedicated online gamer for nigh on ten years now &#8230; I will buy just about any piece of crap developers throw inside a box and ship out to my favorite local retailer. You&#8217;re in my world now. Be afraid, &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/06/13/about-foton/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A dedicated online gamer for nigh on ten years now &#8230; I will buy just about any piece of crap developers throw inside a box and ship out to my favorite local retailer.</p>
<p><strong>You&#8217;re in my world now.  Be afraid, be very afraid.</strong></p>
<p><cite>More about Foton:<br />
  <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/07/15/self-indulgent-introduction/">Self-indulgent introduction</a><br />
  <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2004/10/24/disclaimers-foton-style/">Disclaimers</a></cite></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
