<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>gdc &#8211; AFK Gamer</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/tag/gdc/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/</link>
	<description>Hello.  I see you.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Thu, 07 Aug 2014 11:49:50 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Meet the Blahggers</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/14/meet-the-blahggers/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/14/meet-the-blahggers/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2006 18:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gdc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wordpress]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/14/meet-the-blahggers/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[So this GDC thing is coming up in March. That&#8217;s the Game Developers Conference, and although the name suggests this is for insiders only, money talks &#8212; $1625 for an all-access pass, prices good until tomorrow. I don&#8217;t think that &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/14/meet-the-blahggers/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So this GDC thing is coming up in March.  That&#8217;s the <strong>G</strong>ame <strong>D</strong>evelopers <strong>C</strong>onference, and although the name suggests this is for insiders only, <a href="http://www.gdconf.com/register/passoptions.htm">money talks</a> &#8212; $1625 for an all-access pass, prices good until tomorrow.  </p>
<p>I don&#8217;t think that includes an open bar.  Trust me, I looked.</p>
<p>I read over on <a href="http://www.zenofdesign.com/?p=573">Schubert&#8217;s Zen of Design</a> that he&#8217;s hosting a Game Blogger Meet N Greet in connection with the GDC, which sounds interesting and all, but there is no way in hell I can sell a gaming conference to my boss.  He&#8217;s not a visionary like me.  He&#8217;s good for signing paychecks, however, and providing unrestricted net access.  (<a href="http://www.cmpevents.com/GD06/a.asp?option=C&#038;V=11&#038;SessID=2340">Meet N Greet details</a>)  </p>
<p>Some of the issues up for discussion, which I can answer right now because I&#8217;m good at explaining things:</p>
<p>Privacy issues &#8212; stay anonymous, guard it with your life.  You do like to get paid, don&#8217;t you?  (and, for us outsiders, you don&#8217;t want your account mysteriously banned, do you?)</p>
<p>Troublesome posters and/or spam &#8212; Posters, edit their crap to something more &#8230; syco-fancy.  Some dude thinks he can come into my house (here) where I pay the bills and take a shit, he&#8217;s got another thing coming.  (Way more fun than a blanket IP ban, too.)  Spam, <a href="http://akismet.com/">Akismet</a> and <a href="http://www.ioerror.us/software/bad-behavior/">Bad Behavior</a> for the win.  No auto-moderation necessary.</p>
<p>Best blog software &#8212; It begins and ends with WordPress.</p>
<p>The bar tab &#8212; Invite one of the IGE guys, they&#8217;re rich.</p>
<p>Probably the best piece of advice I could offer to wannabes, startups and blogger hags alike would be this, (not that I was asked):  Take a stand on something.  Fanbois, suckups and company mouthpieces we have aplenty.  </p>
<p>Your best work will always start off with &#8220;I just had a crazy idea&#8221;.  </p>
<p>Conversely, not every crazy idea will be good work.  We want to read that too.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/14/meet-the-blahggers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>IGF Student Showcase Winners</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/01/16/igf-student-showcase-winners/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/01/16/igf-student-showcase-winners/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2006 20:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Asides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[awards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gdc]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/01/16/igf-student-showcase-winners/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Via Gamasutra, a gaming insider&#8217;s news site, 2006 IGF Student Showcase Winners Announced. Winning games will be featured at the 2006 GDC. You can try out many of the games yourself, like Cloud, a goofy flying game without orcs or &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/01/16/igf-student-showcase-winners/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Via Gamasutra, a gaming insider&#8217;s news site, <a href="http://www.gamasutra.com/php-bin/news_index.php?story=7795">2006 IGF Student Showcase Winners Announced</a>.  Winning games will be featured at the 2006 <a href="http://www.gdconf.com/">GDC</a>.  You can try out many of the games yourself, like Cloud, a goofy flying game without orcs or superheroes.  If I had to battle flying orc superheroes, then they&#8217;d really have something there!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/01/16/igf-student-showcase-winners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Thing We Do, We Kill All the Poets&#8482;</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/14/pffft-where-does-she-get-off/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/14/pffft-where-does-she-get-off/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2005 07:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gdc]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/14/pffft-where-does-she-get-off/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Curious Game Designers&#8217; Challenge at the GDC thing this year: the Emily Dickinson license. And when I say &#8220;curious,&#8221; I mean &#8220;what the fuck could they have been thinking?&#8221; The contestants did the best they could with the lame ass &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/14/pffft-where-does-she-get-off/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Curious Game Designers&#8217; Challenge at the GDC thing this year:  <a href="http://www.gamespy.com/articles/594/594861p1.html">the Emily Dickinson license</a>.</p>
<p>And when I say &#8220;curious,&#8221; I mean &#8220;what the fuck could they have been thinking?&#8221;</p>
<p>The contestants did the best they could with the lame ass material they were given:</p>
<blockquote><p>What if YOU were in charge of a game development company that had just landed the license for the complete works of Emily Dickinson, one of the greatest American Poets of all time? What game would you create? </p></blockquote>
<p>Hey, because she could not stop for Death, He kindly stopped for her.  End of story.  </p>
<p>(Not soon enough in my opinion, but that&#8217;s another post.)</p>
<p>I&#8217;m hoping this might make next year&#8217;s challenge:</p>
<p><img src="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/images/Lewt.JPG" width="337" height="55" alt="We&#8217;d like any reward, kthx." /></p>
<p>Why is risk versus reward such a hard concept to understand?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/14/pffft-where-does-she-get-off/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prank Sense Tingling!</title>
		<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/08/prank-sense-tingling/</link>
				<comments>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/08/prank-sense-tingling/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2005 18:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Etc.]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gdc]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/07/prank-sense-tingling/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[So, you probably know that alot of the wigs are at this 2005 GDC thing. (ffs, I just told you that yesterday. Blackout issues!) Obviously, I&#8217;m not there or I&#8217;d be doing a crass live blogging schtick that would mostly &#8230; <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/08/prank-sense-tingling/">Continue reading <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So, you probably know that alot of the wigs are at this <a href="http://www.gdconf.com/">2005 GDC thing</a>.  (<acronym title="for fuck's sake">ffs</acronym>, I just told you that yesterday.  Blackout issues!)</p>
<p>Obviously, I&#8217;m not there or I&#8217;d be doing a crass live blogging schtick that would mostly fall flat but occasionally be killer &#8230; or so I imagine.  Anytime a group of my arch enemies is gathered in a single location, milling about, I entertain prank fantasies.</p>
<p>This is what life has reduced me to &#8230; prank fantasies.</p>
<p>I present &#8230; (if I had all the time in the world and all the money, too) My Top Five List of GDC Pranks:</p>
<p><span id="more-338"></span>1.  Order 30 Pizza Hut pizzas for delivery to one of the conference dinners.</p>
<p>2.  Run around to the different Room Placards for roundtables and hourly sessions, etc. and tape a sign underneath that reads:  IGE &#8220;Consultants&#8221; Reception in Room 1305, immediately following.  Heh, I&#8217;d bag quite a few of the curious and rabid at the elevators &#8230; uncertain how to find Floor 13, but determined to do so.</p>
<p>3.  A mysterious (and set to LOUD) ringing cellphone at a dramatic moment in the keynote speech:  (answerer stands up in a panic and signals the speaker to pause)  It&#8217;s God!  His Warcraft server is down!  (You just know some of the Blizzard Collective is there.  Probably enduring all the snide dev jokes, too.)</p>
<p>For these next few, I&#8217;d need to infiltrate the convention center with a few props.  Trust me, enough money, enough time, I can do anything.  A booth, rented to the Dragons Online LLC (ffs, I don&#8217;t want to get sued).</p>
<p>4.  Real life quests, kind of like Gaming Companies do at their own fan fests, but with a twist.  They&#8217;re like gaming quests where the pieces never fucking drop.  Examples:  find an alcoholic drink under 3 bucks within 3 miles of the convention center, good pizza ANYWHERE in California (I speak the truth), and take a cab to a &#8220;questionable neighborhood&#8221; in Oakland and convince a homey out on the street after midnight to buy your box and purchase a 6-month subscription.  (4TW on that one.  Anyone that can do that wins EverQuest and a t-shirt.)</p>
<p>5.  Set up a few computers at the Fake Gaming LLC booth with some DVDs looping.  Examples:  Napoleon Dynamite &#8230; tagline:  A boy, some <a href="http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=liger&#038;defid=761434">ligers</a>, this could work!, The Ring &#8230; tagline:  Become the undead, but not vampires, because that is so <a href="http://www.mythic-realms.com/darknessfalls.htm">Darkness Falls</a>!, Gladiator &#8230; tagline:  You know you want to dual wield!, I, Robot &#8230; tagline:  Be a human, be a robot &#8212; in the future, it&#8217;s all the same!, The Matrix &#8230; tagline:  There&#8217;s still time to buy in on this one!.</p>
<p>If only designing pranks was a profession; it&#8217;s my true calling, I think.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/03/08/prank-sense-tingling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
