<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Same As It Ever Was	</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/</link>
	<description>Hello.  I see you.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Tue, 28 Feb 2017 12:33:23 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
			<item>
				<title>
				By: S. Labyrinth				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16086</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[S. Labyrinth]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 06:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16086</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[I always thought Guild Wars nicely balanced PvE and PvP. I had a blast on all of my characters;  in the end there just wasn&#039;t enough PvE content to keep me around long-term.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I always thought Guild Wars nicely balanced PvE and PvP. I had a blast on all of my characters;  in the end there just wasn&#8217;t enough PvE content to keep me around long-term.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Random Poster				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16084</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Random Poster]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 05:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16084</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[&lt;blockquote&gt;Blizzard was pretty good at balance,&lt;/blockquote&gt;

There fixed that for you.

They stopped being good at balancing when they let BG/Arena PvP start dictating changes made to the PvE side of things.

Same problem every MMO has when they don&#039;t have some kind of separate system from PvE stats and PvP /shrug]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Blizzard was pretty good at balance,</p></blockquote>
<p>There fixed that for you.</p>
<p>They stopped being good at balancing when they let BG/Arena PvP start dictating changes made to the PvE side of things.</p>
<p>Same problem every MMO has when they don&#8217;t have some kind of separate system from PvE stats and PvP /shrug</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Saylah				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16081</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saylah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2007 02:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16081</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[I remember posting my early thoughts about my priest pretty much being DOA before TBC ever came out.  But I&#039;d already gotten used to the pain so the new content would suffice to re-create the fun factor.  Unfortunately, the continued nerfing just shakes loose too much of the pleasure.

Like another commenter said - balance is one thing, but killing the fun factor is another.  I visited almost all of the class forums last night.  I was really shocked to see so many of the classes up in arms.  I expected the Priests, Druids and Paladins to be upset.  I dunno what Rogues are whinning for and seeing Mages crying foul was comical.  The only forum that didnt disappoint were the Warlocks who were amusing themselves with silly lets play on the forum posts.  That&#039;s how you know which classes are probably over powered.  They&#039;re making nice on the forums cuz well, life&#039;s good and nothing to fret over. LOL  Why o why, did I give my kid my warlock??]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I remember posting my early thoughts about my priest pretty much being DOA before TBC ever came out.  But I&#8217;d already gotten used to the pain so the new content would suffice to re-create the fun factor.  Unfortunately, the continued nerfing just shakes loose too much of the pleasure.</p>
<p>Like another commenter said &#8211; balance is one thing, but killing the fun factor is another.  I visited almost all of the class forums last night.  I was really shocked to see so many of the classes up in arms.  I expected the Priests, Druids and Paladins to be upset.  I dunno what Rogues are whinning for and seeing Mages crying foul was comical.  The only forum that didnt disappoint were the Warlocks who were amusing themselves with silly lets play on the forum posts.  That&#8217;s how you know which classes are probably over powered.  They&#8217;re making nice on the forums cuz well, life&#8217;s good and nothing to fret over. LOL  Why o why, did I give my kid my warlock??</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Rose				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16067</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rose]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 20:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16067</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[The reason why people like to reminisce about the &quot;good old days&quot; of MUDs, IRC networks, old school DOS games, text-only BBS&#039;s, etc. is because those were times when the online genre was getting its beginnings, the community was much smaller, and just about everyone was a hardcore nerd and true geek.

Also, people like to think that despite the tendency for history to repeat itself, the past is still more glorious and poignant than the present.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The reason why people like to reminisce about the &#8220;good old days&#8221; of MUDs, IRC networks, old school DOS games, text-only BBS&#8217;s, etc. is because those were times when the online genre was getting its beginnings, the community was much smaller, and just about everyone was a hardcore nerd and true geek.</p>
<p>Also, people like to think that despite the tendency for history to repeat itself, the past is still more glorious and poignant than the present.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Glazius				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16061</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Glazius]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16061</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[I hate hate HATE that mudwimping guide and the people who quote it.

Because it assumes a static population of players and then goes from there to say &quot;there are some people who will hate any change, and some people who will always hate you, therefore NEVER CHANGE ANYTHING or your game spirals into destruction&quot;.

And this is supposed to be some deep and profound insight?

--GF]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I hate hate HATE that mudwimping guide and the people who quote it.</p>
<p>Because it assumes a static population of players and then goes from there to say &#8220;there are some people who will hate any change, and some people who will always hate you, therefore NEVER CHANGE ANYTHING or your game spirals into destruction&#8221;.</p>
<p>And this is supposed to be some deep and profound insight?</p>
<p>&#8211;GF</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Rose				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16053</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rose]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 17:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16053</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nerf

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nerf_%28computer_gaming%29

 nerf is a change to the rules of a computer game that weakens a certain object or ability.

The term comes from the childsafe Nerf toys of soft foam and plastic, which are often made in the shape of guns, bats, or other weapons. The term originated in the MMORPG Ultima Online, where for a long period of time the sword skill was incredibly powerful. The designers eventually lowered its effectiveness, causing massive player outcry; they claimed that it seemed as though they were hitting with &quot;Nerf Bats&quot;.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nerf" rel="nofollow">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nerf</a></p>
<p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nerf_%28computer_gaming%29" rel="nofollow">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nerf_%28computer_gaming%29</a></p>
<p> nerf is a change to the rules of a computer game that weakens a certain object or ability.</p>
<p>The term comes from the childsafe Nerf toys of soft foam and plastic, which are often made in the shape of guns, bats, or other weapons. The term originated in the MMORPG Ultima Online, where for a long period of time the sword skill was incredibly powerful. The designers eventually lowered its effectiveness, causing massive player outcry; they claimed that it seemed as though they were hitting with &#8220;Nerf Bats&#8221;.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Vargen				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16049</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Vargen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 17:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16049</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[I think the term &quot;nerfing&quot; came from Ultima Online; when the first major rebalancing greatly reduced the damage that melee weapons did people started saying it felt like their swords were made out of Nerf(tm) foam because of how lightly they hit. And since nerfing has a better ring to it than wimping it stuck.

Or it may have pre-dated UO and just caught on there with the analogy intact. I dunno.

Blizzard&#039;s pretty good at balance, but they made some real screwups this time out. Most of this is due to itemization issues it looks like, what with the new standards of armor and stamina not playing well with the established standards for healing and druid bonuses (note to designers: multplicative bonuses are a BITCH to balance). Hopefully the nerfs will pave the way for making the higher-end items not suck without being too overwhelming.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I think the term &#8220;nerfing&#8221; came from Ultima Online; when the first major rebalancing greatly reduced the damage that melee weapons did people started saying it felt like their swords were made out of Nerf(tm) foam because of how lightly they hit. And since nerfing has a better ring to it than wimping it stuck.</p>
<p>Or it may have pre-dated UO and just caught on there with the analogy intact. I dunno.</p>
<p>Blizzard&#8217;s pretty good at balance, but they made some real screwups this time out. Most of this is due to itemization issues it looks like, what with the new standards of armor and stamina not playing well with the established standards for healing and druid bonuses (note to designers: multplicative bonuses are a BITCH to balance). Hopefully the nerfs will pave the way for making the higher-end items not suck without being too overwhelming.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Rose				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16048</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rose]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 16:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16048</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[My fiance used to play MUDs, and we&#039;ve played various MMORPGs and online RPGs for years.  The endless cycles of nerfs are always the same, but usually people just take it all in stride because they still enjoy the game.  It&#039;s only when the fun itself stops that people get really upset about the nerfs, and consider quitting / actually quit.  FOTM was invented due to the endless cycles of nerfs, you know.

For me, the fun factor was not there anymore as I played my 70 priest, and then the nerfs come.  They rapidly diminished all other reasons I had for wanting to advance my character.  There are outside motivators like the people you play with, but when there are several classes that outperform you, and your friends are happily playing those classes, it&#039;s easy to feel like giving a new game a try.

Ultimately, I can&#039;t help but think back to the other games I&#039;d poured a lot of time and passion into, and wonder where that passion went.  All games nerf, it&#039;s just inevitable.  But to do so in the name of &quot;balance&quot; is stupid, since you can upgrade those that are lesser in order to make the game more fun for everyone.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My fiance used to play MUDs, and we&#8217;ve played various MMORPGs and online RPGs for years.  The endless cycles of nerfs are always the same, but usually people just take it all in stride because they still enjoy the game.  It&#8217;s only when the fun itself stops that people get really upset about the nerfs, and consider quitting / actually quit.  FOTM was invented due to the endless cycles of nerfs, you know.</p>
<p>For me, the fun factor was not there anymore as I played my 70 priest, and then the nerfs come.  They rapidly diminished all other reasons I had for wanting to advance my character.  There are outside motivators like the people you play with, but when there are several classes that outperform you, and your friends are happily playing those classes, it&#8217;s easy to feel like giving a new game a try.</p>
<p>Ultimately, I can&#8217;t help but think back to the other games I&#8217;d poured a lot of time and passion into, and wonder where that passion went.  All games nerf, it&#8217;s just inevitable.  But to do so in the name of &#8220;balance&#8221; is stupid, since you can upgrade those that are lesser in order to make the game more fun for everyone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Tara				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/comment-page-1/#comment-16047</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tara]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 16:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2007/03/06/same-as-it-ever-was/#comment-16047</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Just a nitpick - &quot;Our forefathers played these around a kitchen table&quot; - MUDs were (and are) online.  And since I doubt our forefathers had laptops, they were playing them in the dark dank holes of basement computer rooms, much like our current generation.  Just without the pretty graphics.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just a nitpick &#8211; &#8220;Our forefathers played these around a kitchen table&#8221; &#8211; MUDs were (and are) online.  And since I doubt our forefathers had laptops, they were playing them in the dark dank holes of basement computer rooms, much like our current generation.  Just without the pretty graphics.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
			</channel>
</rss>
