<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: It Was a Stupid Idea Then and It&#8217;s Still Stupid	</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/</link>
	<description>Hello.  I see you.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Tue, 28 Feb 2017 12:33:23 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
			<item>
				<title>
				By: litfuse				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2600</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[litfuse]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2006 04:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2600</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[it is the fate of all mmos to become so broken they are beyond repair

you can thank money for this]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>it is the fate of all mmos to become so broken they are beyond repair</p>
<p>you can thank money for this</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Mischiefblog » Blog Archive » Here’s the part where I whine and moan				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2597</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mischiefblog » Blog Archive » Here’s the part where I whine and moan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2006 18:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2597</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[[...] As seen on AFKGamer (and I’m late to the party too–I hate when my real life interferes with my blog reading):  Because that was such a fabulous idea in EQ, it&#039;s bound to be just as popular in Warcraft. O_O [...]]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[&#8230;] As seen on AFKGamer (and I’m late to the party too–I hate when my real life interferes with my blog reading):  Because that was such a fabulous idea in EQ, it&#8217;s bound to be just as popular in Warcraft. O_O [&#8230;]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: TheeNickster				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2589</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeNickster]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2006 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2589</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Good points about their being &quot;carrot&#039;s on a stick&quot; in single and group content. Like you guys, I don&#039;t believe you should always solo in an MMO. Problem is, group content blows chunks in the endgame too. Only when 40 players get together do you have any hope of bettering your character.

What&#039;s really missing in the end game is the short term goals that keep you motivated. These were provided by items and dinging levels. EQ solved the &quot;level cap&quot; problem with AA&#039;s Krones mentioned. Really what they did was &quot;secretly&quot; remove the level cap.

So is that the answer? Should we nuke the level cap and let people grind it up? What about another good EQ invention, LDoN? These were group missions you had to use some skill (not much though) to successfully complete. You were even ranked against other players by win % and total wins, so there was a scoreboard. 

With a scoreboard go bragging rights, and we all love the bragging rights. See, there&#039;s ideas out there, too bad the people that are paid to think about this stuff have quit trying...]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Good points about their being &#8220;carrot&#8217;s on a stick&#8221; in single and group content. Like you guys, I don&#8217;t believe you should always solo in an MMO. Problem is, group content blows chunks in the endgame too. Only when 40 players get together do you have any hope of bettering your character.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s really missing in the end game is the short term goals that keep you motivated. These were provided by items and dinging levels. EQ solved the &#8220;level cap&#8221; problem with AA&#8217;s Krones mentioned. Really what they did was &#8220;secretly&#8221; remove the level cap.</p>
<p>So is that the answer? Should we nuke the level cap and let people grind it up? What about another good EQ invention, LDoN? These were group missions you had to use some skill (not much though) to successfully complete. You were even ranked against other players by win % and total wins, so there was a scoreboard. </p>
<p>With a scoreboard go bragging rights, and we all love the bragging rights. See, there&#8217;s ideas out there, too bad the people that are paid to think about this stuff have quit trying&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Krones				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2587</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Krones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 18:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2587</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[The whole journey of a character is primarily based on incentives after the initial hook wanes, WoW did a great job by making goals accessible in short bursts, etc. Incentives prop up and support most of the motive behind item centric worlds and achiever playtypes. The basic rags to riches concept.

When players reach a cap in their overall progression they face an invisible wall, the ultimate cockblock. Well I&#039;ve made it this far, now what? I&#039;m screwed because I don&#039;t raid and the other systems to keep me occupied at this point in my progression are boring.  

Removing or branching out exclusive incentives obtained in the raid structure isn&#039;t a good solution, but that&#039;s just me, in fact, I haven&#039;t raided in over a year so I don&#039;t think I would miss that structure at all, but the world would just end up being like a throw-away single player experience in the end without these systems supporting retention, players will still hit those invisible walls if all high-end loot is obtained by the same type of structured content players churned through during 1-60. We could always go back and point the blame on two developers who played EQ. 

Other thoughts: 

If the leveling curve were tuned in upwards to at least 25 days played it would have helped, the content was in place to support a longer leveling curve. The current average  is 15-18 days played for begiginners, the current time investment is based off empirical data collected by playon. 

AA system in EverQuest was a great way for non raiders to progress their incentives after hitting the wall (still boring) even if it bridged the gap between raiders and non further than it should have.

PvP is a great retention system if implemented correctly, World of Warcraft&#039;s pvp system is poorly designed.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The whole journey of a character is primarily based on incentives after the initial hook wanes, WoW did a great job by making goals accessible in short bursts, etc. Incentives prop up and support most of the motive behind item centric worlds and achiever playtypes. The basic rags to riches concept.</p>
<p>When players reach a cap in their overall progression they face an invisible wall, the ultimate cockblock. Well I&#8217;ve made it this far, now what? I&#8217;m screwed because I don&#8217;t raid and the other systems to keep me occupied at this point in my progression are boring.  </p>
<p>Removing or branching out exclusive incentives obtained in the raid structure isn&#8217;t a good solution, but that&#8217;s just me, in fact, I haven&#8217;t raided in over a year so I don&#8217;t think I would miss that structure at all, but the world would just end up being like a throw-away single player experience in the end without these systems supporting retention, players will still hit those invisible walls if all high-end loot is obtained by the same type of structured content players churned through during 1-60. We could always go back and point the blame on two developers who played EQ. </p>
<p>Other thoughts: </p>
<p>If the leveling curve were tuned in upwards to at least 25 days played it would have helped, the content was in place to support a longer leveling curve. The current average  is 15-18 days played for begiginners, the current time investment is based off empirical data collected by playon. </p>
<p>AA system in EverQuest was a great way for non raiders to progress their incentives after hitting the wall (still boring) even if it bridged the gap between raiders and non further than it should have.</p>
<p>PvP is a great retention system if implemented correctly, World of Warcraft&#8217;s pvp system is poorly designed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Kranky Kraut				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2586</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kranky Kraut]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 16:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2586</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Many people dislike raid-centric end-game content. Hell, even I do. I burn out fast. But unless someone can come up with a good alternative that isn&#039;t PvP, I find it rather useless to complain about it.

I disagree that WoW would be a better game if the life post-60 was more like life pre-60 because I don&#039;t feel like grinding ogres day after day - or even worse, running 100 shitty collection quests that drive you insane. Fuck soloing.

Yes, certainly you need phat lewts as an incentive for raiding but that doesn&#039;t make raiding a game mechanic that is worse than some other play style. I mean, I certainly wouldn&#039;t do group or solo content if there wasn&#039;t an incentive either. Would you?]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many people dislike raid-centric end-game content. Hell, even I do. I burn out fast. But unless someone can come up with a good alternative that isn&#8217;t PvP, I find it rather useless to complain about it.</p>
<p>I disagree that WoW would be a better game if the life post-60 was more like life pre-60 because I don&#8217;t feel like grinding ogres day after day &#8211; or even worse, running 100 shitty collection quests that drive you insane. Fuck soloing.</p>
<p>Yes, certainly you need phat lewts as an incentive for raiding but that doesn&#8217;t make raiding a game mechanic that is worse than some other play style. I mean, I certainly wouldn&#8217;t do group or solo content if there wasn&#8217;t an incentive either. Would you?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: TheeNickster				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2585</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeNickster]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 15:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2585</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[I couldn&#039;t actually tell you if I&#039;d want WoW to be more like Guildwars because I haven&#039;t played Guildwars. I can say that WoW would be a much better game if the life post-60 were more like the life pre-60. As a &quot;retired&quot; raider though, I can tell you that once you hit 60, it&#039;s game over unless you like to raid. Or maybe you could turn pro as a  gold farmer, because if I&#039;m whispering &quot;ni hao&quot; you couldn&#039;t tell me from the real pro&#039;s. I can also tell you that gold farming for equipment is a mind numbingly dull way to live.

I&#039;m retired from raiding because PoP turned me into a bitter old cynic. I know why you guys raid, it&#039;s all about the loot, and I mean ALL about the loot. Your not exited about doing your 1000&#039;th run through MC, but your new recruits need phat lewts. So you drag yourself (and your other vets) through three more hours of the same crap you&#039;ve done for 6 months. Heck, some of your vets are so bored their writing blogs to pass the time.

Yet whenever someone suggests that raid style loot be gained from non-raid sources it&#039;s still high treason against the gods. &quot;Don&#039;t those clueless newbs know that if no loot dropped on the raids, nobody would raid?&quot; Well that&#039;s kindof our point. Since raiding is a game mechanic that requires incentive to prop it up it&#039;s a bad play mechanic.

No matter what your current style of play is, the first MMO that comes up with an end game that&#039;s &quot;fun&quot; will make all others (including WoW) obsolete. As for how a developer would do that, our best guess is simply &quot;make it more like it was when we we&#039;re newbs&quot;...]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I couldn&#8217;t actually tell you if I&#8217;d want WoW to be more like Guildwars because I haven&#8217;t played Guildwars. I can say that WoW would be a much better game if the life post-60 were more like the life pre-60. As a &#8220;retired&#8221; raider though, I can tell you that once you hit 60, it&#8217;s game over unless you like to raid. Or maybe you could turn pro as a  gold farmer, because if I&#8217;m whispering &#8220;ni hao&#8221; you couldn&#8217;t tell me from the real pro&#8217;s. I can also tell you that gold farming for equipment is a mind numbingly dull way to live.</p>
<p>I&#8217;m retired from raiding because PoP turned me into a bitter old cynic. I know why you guys raid, it&#8217;s all about the loot, and I mean ALL about the loot. Your not exited about doing your 1000&#8217;th run through MC, but your new recruits need phat lewts. So you drag yourself (and your other vets) through three more hours of the same crap you&#8217;ve done for 6 months. Heck, some of your vets are so bored their writing blogs to pass the time.</p>
<p>Yet whenever someone suggests that raid style loot be gained from non-raid sources it&#8217;s still high treason against the gods. &#8220;Don&#8217;t those clueless newbs know that if no loot dropped on the raids, nobody would raid?&#8221; Well that&#8217;s kindof our point. Since raiding is a game mechanic that requires incentive to prop it up it&#8217;s a bad play mechanic.</p>
<p>No matter what your current style of play is, the first MMO that comes up with an end game that&#8217;s &#8220;fun&#8221; will make all others (including WoW) obsolete. As for how a developer would do that, our best guess is simply &#8220;make it more like it was when we we&#8217;re newbs&#8221;&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Krones				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2584</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Krones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 04:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2584</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Well, it&#039;s more like the design at the cap doesn&#039;t support the expansion of casual content mainly because of other systems like the itemization. They need to distinguish the rewards, ie: situational itemization so the devs can implement more casual content and allow all players to progress via items, but at the same time keeping those &quot;raiding&quot; rewards lucrative and entice casual players into participating in 20-40 player content.  

I can use the same example with the spell drops in high end dungeons that Foton addressed above, if you make them situational, you can come up with some fucked up shit that would be a lot of fun instead of the standard incremental shit you have now and casuals won&#039;t have to stress about getting their &quot;core&quot; spells with a 40 man crew so they can do their own content. The downside is with softcaps and making more items situational you sort of penalize the hardcore rewards and a lot of the smarter catasses will be pissed off about the artificial barrier, but if they spend most of their time raiding and killing the big shit, fuck it. They can always have both anyway. 

Do you want WoW to be like Guildwars? If you want to play Guildwars go play Guildwars or you can wait for Hellgate: London.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well, it&#8217;s more like the design at the cap doesn&#8217;t support the expansion of casual content mainly because of other systems like the itemization. They need to distinguish the rewards, ie: situational itemization so the devs can implement more casual content and allow all players to progress via items, but at the same time keeping those &#8220;raiding&#8221; rewards lucrative and entice casual players into participating in 20-40 player content.  </p>
<p>I can use the same example with the spell drops in high end dungeons that Foton addressed above, if you make them situational, you can come up with some fucked up shit that would be a lot of fun instead of the standard incremental shit you have now and casuals won&#8217;t have to stress about getting their &#8220;core&#8221; spells with a 40 man crew so they can do their own content. The downside is with softcaps and making more items situational you sort of penalize the hardcore rewards and a lot of the smarter catasses will be pissed off about the artificial barrier, but if they spend most of their time raiding and killing the big shit, fuck it. They can always have both anyway. </p>
<p>Do you want WoW to be like Guildwars? If you want to play Guildwars go play Guildwars or you can wait for Hellgate: London.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: TheeNickster				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2582</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[TheeNickster]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2006 00:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2582</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[I&#039;ll tell you why WoW is turning into World of Raidcraft. The original designers of the game all got paid bigger bucks jump ship for Guildwars. To replace them, they hired ex-EQ&#039;ers. Apparently these dev&#039;s learned nothing from driving EQ into the ground.

Blizz needs to whip out big time dollars to get their original designers back. That or they could rename Ironforge to &quot;Plane of Knowledge&quot; so people aren&#039;t so confused....]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ll tell you why WoW is turning into World of Raidcraft. The original designers of the game all got paid bigger bucks jump ship for Guildwars. To replace them, they hired ex-EQ&#8217;ers. Apparently these dev&#8217;s learned nothing from driving EQ into the ground.</p>
<p>Blizz needs to whip out big time dollars to get their original designers back. That or they could rename Ironforge to &#8220;Plane of Knowledge&#8221; so people aren&#8217;t so confused&#8230;.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Ninefingers				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2580</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ninefingers]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2006 21:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2580</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[KrankyKraut,

You are correct in what you are saying. Are you a Raider yourself?

Anyway I feel you are not, at least to my understanding, discussing what Foton&#039;s argument or thoughts on this matter are. I see him saying that when a company starts putting items and content in places where over 50% of the players can&#039;t get them, they are hurting themselves and other players. (Btw, saying 50% is being VERRRRRRRY lenient on who can get AQ items.)

Let&#039;s see if quotes work or if I can use them correctly:

&lt;blockquote&gt;You don&#039;t _have_ to farm anything. There were guilds capable of farming BWL in one session before AQ was even released. You certainly don&#039;t need these spells in order to beat any content currently available in the game.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

I&#039;m not sure if we&#039;re playing the same game. Items are everything. Sure, it may not make THAT big a difference in PVE battles, but when the WARcraft part of the game kicks in, anyone loaded with epics will wipe the floor with the regular green/blue player. If the game is supposed to be about PVP, why make the best items not available for the majority of your players. (No one has an I WIN button, but having Epics make an insane amount of difference in PVP situations.)

The expansion will make areas like MC, ZG, and higher-end content available to those Foton are speaking of, but then the higher ups will have more Raider only toys to play with.

Back to Foton&#039;s point though: Why is Blizzard going down the same road as EQ in content and items? Aren&#039;t there more creative and better ways of putting this kind of content into the game? (I have no ideas myself. Then again, I&#039;m not paid to come up with these ideas either.)

Ninefingers]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KrankyKraut,</p>
<p>You are correct in what you are saying. Are you a Raider yourself?</p>
<p>Anyway I feel you are not, at least to my understanding, discussing what Foton&#8217;s argument or thoughts on this matter are. I see him saying that when a company starts putting items and content in places where over 50% of the players can&#8217;t get them, they are hurting themselves and other players. (Btw, saying 50% is being VERRRRRRRY lenient on who can get AQ items.)</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s see if quotes work or if I can use them correctly:</p>
<blockquote><p>You don&#8217;t _have_ to farm anything. There were guilds capable of farming BWL in one session before AQ was even released. You certainly don&#8217;t need these spells in order to beat any content currently available in the game.</p></blockquote>
<p>I&#8217;m not sure if we&#8217;re playing the same game. Items are everything. Sure, it may not make THAT big a difference in PVE battles, but when the WARcraft part of the game kicks in, anyone loaded with epics will wipe the floor with the regular green/blue player. If the game is supposed to be about PVP, why make the best items not available for the majority of your players. (No one has an I WIN button, but having Epics make an insane amount of difference in PVP situations.)</p>
<p>The expansion will make areas like MC, ZG, and higher-end content available to those Foton are speaking of, but then the higher ups will have more Raider only toys to play with.</p>
<p>Back to Foton&#8217;s point though: Why is Blizzard going down the same road as EQ in content and items? Aren&#8217;t there more creative and better ways of putting this kind of content into the game? (I have no ideas myself. Then again, I&#8217;m not paid to come up with these ideas either.)</p>
<p>Ninefingers</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Kranky Kraut				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/comment-page-1/#comment-2578</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kranky Kraut]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2006 18:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2006/02/24/it-was-a-stupid-idea-then-and-its-still-stupid/#comment-2578</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[You need to have a good look at the spell/skill upgrades. Most melee upgrades are rather tiny. 

There is also another point we&#039;ve all missed so far: selling these spells to the lvl 60 strat/scholo/UBRS/DM crowd would make these instances too easy.

A raid guild is most likely decked out in epic gear of at least MC or ZG quality. They have a ton of  dmg items, high DPS weapons, plus the secondary AP/Crit increases through the massive stat upgrades that epic armor provides. The base damage is only one part of the calculation. 

So while a new spell rank might be a great upgrade for someone who&#039;s just starting with UBRS and Strat, it&#039;s actually not that much of an upgrade for hardcore raiders.

A MC/ZG equipped Mage likely has a couple of hundred points in  dmg and both trinkets (TOeP, ZHC). Upgrading his Fireball&#039;s or Frostbolt&#039;s base damage would prolly only constitute a minor relative upgrade of his total damage output. It wouldn&#039;t make much of a difference against BWL raid mobs. 

Upgrading the base damage of a a green/blue UBRS PuGer on the other hand would be a significant upgrade that could potentially trivialze the content.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You need to have a good look at the spell/skill upgrades. Most melee upgrades are rather tiny. </p>
<p>There is also another point we&#8217;ve all missed so far: selling these spells to the lvl 60 strat/scholo/UBRS/DM crowd would make these instances too easy.</p>
<p>A raid guild is most likely decked out in epic gear of at least MC or ZG quality. They have a ton of  dmg items, high DPS weapons, plus the secondary AP/Crit increases through the massive stat upgrades that epic armor provides. The base damage is only one part of the calculation. </p>
<p>So while a new spell rank might be a great upgrade for someone who&#8217;s just starting with UBRS and Strat, it&#8217;s actually not that much of an upgrade for hardcore raiders.</p>
<p>A MC/ZG equipped Mage likely has a couple of hundred points in  dmg and both trinkets (TOeP, ZHC). Upgrading his Fireball&#8217;s or Frostbolt&#8217;s base damage would prolly only constitute a minor relative upgrade of his total damage output. It wouldn&#8217;t make much of a difference against BWL raid mobs. </p>
<p>Upgrading the base damage of a a green/blue UBRS PuGer on the other hand would be a significant upgrade that could potentially trivialze the content.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
			</channel>
</rss>
