<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Warcraft Widows	</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/</link>
	<description>Hello.  I see you.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Tue, 28 Feb 2017 12:33:23 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
			<item>
				<title>
				By: Foton				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16500</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Foton]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 14:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16500</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Dear Widows and Gamers&#039; Significant Others,

I appreciate all the stories you&#039;ve told and the advice you&#039;ve offered.  I wish there were easy answers -- it&#039;s obvious there&#039;s not.

Unfortunately, this thread has grown to monster proportions and threatens to tear the very fabric of time and space.  Thanks to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com&quot;/ rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;AFK Gamer&lt;/a&gt; sponsors, I can offer you a new home to share your experiences and tell your stories if you&#039;d like.

I&#039;ve set up a small forum area where you&#039;re free to continue the discussion or begin new ones:  the &lt;a href=&quot;https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/forums/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;AFK Gamer forums&lt;/a&gt;.  The forums are powered by bbPress and don&#039;t have bells and whistles, but they should be sufficient for conversation.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/forums/forum/3&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The Widows&lt;/a&gt; sub-forum is just for you guys.  (Gamers, you are on a short leash in that forum.  Behave or I can make you behave.)

I&#039;m closing comments here, but if you have problems with the forums, you can always contact me at foton(at)afkgamer.com.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dear Widows and Gamers&#8217; Significant Others,</p>
<p>I appreciate all the stories you&#8217;ve told and the advice you&#8217;ve offered.  I wish there were easy answers &#8212; it&#8217;s obvious there&#8217;s not.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this thread has grown to monster proportions and threatens to tear the very fabric of time and space.  Thanks to the <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/" rel="nofollow">AFK Gamer</a> sponsors, I can offer you a new home to share your experiences and tell your stories if you&#8217;d like.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve set up a small forum area where you&#8217;re free to continue the discussion or begin new ones:  the <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/forums/" rel="nofollow">AFK Gamer forums</a>.  The forums are powered by bbPress and don&#8217;t have bells and whistles, but they should be sufficient for conversation.  <a href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/forums/forum/3" rel="nofollow">The Widows</a> sub-forum is just for you guys.  (Gamers, you are on a short leash in that forum.  Behave or I can make you behave.)</p>
<p>I&#8217;m closing comments here, but if you have problems with the forums, you can always contact me at foton(at)afkgamer.com.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: angie carter				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16498</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[angie carter]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 13:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16498</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[&#039;LMAO&#039; you&#039;re way too p*ssed off to be neutral, so what&#039;s your story or are you one of the widow&#039;s dead husbands........shirty because it&#039;s easier than taking responsibility for your actions, you sound angry at yourself.
And as for WOWChick well, don&#039;t really need to say anything, you&#039;re a joke.
RL Guy, hope you are happy in the future and she realises what an a*se she&#039;s been. Another Kate, I&#039;ve enjoyed your calm, rational posts, thank you

Rebecca, leave him, you aren&#039;t trapped yet, if he&#039;s like this now it&#039;ll only get worse.

Now can all the nasty people on here just butt out, leave us alone to winge, you are obviously not reading the posts properly!]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8216;LMAO&#8217; you&#8217;re way too p*ssed off to be neutral, so what&#8217;s your story or are you one of the widow&#8217;s dead husbands&#8230;&#8230;..shirty because it&#8217;s easier than taking responsibility for your actions, you sound angry at yourself.<br />
And as for WOWChick well, don&#8217;t really need to say anything, you&#8217;re a joke.<br />
RL Guy, hope you are happy in the future and she realises what an a*se she&#8217;s been. Another Kate, I&#8217;ve enjoyed your calm, rational posts, thank you</p>
<p>Rebecca, leave him, you aren&#8217;t trapped yet, if he&#8217;s like this now it&#8217;ll only get worse.</p>
<p>Now can all the nasty people on here just butt out, leave us alone to winge, you are obviously not reading the posts properly!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Rebecca				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16474</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Rebecca]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 02:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16474</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Well,  I don&#039;t know what to say to any of this because I&#039;m only 16.  I have a boyfriend who is completely drowning in world of warcraft, and I don&#039;t really care that he wants to play, or whatever.  It&#039;s his choice.  But what pisses me off is that he won&#039;t give me a few minutes to say &quot;Hi, how are you?&quot; Instead, like he did on friday, he opens the door and runs back so he can finish his game and mind you, he lives in a building. I was made to walk 3 flights by myself in a place I&#039;ve only been to three times in my life. Last night, I wanted to talk to him about being a little rude lately, and I wanted to ask him to lay off a bit, to which he laughed and didn&#039;t take me seriously. He thought I was being accusatory and I was wrongfully accusing him of things he didn&#039;t do. Believe me, and I think all girls will agree, but you just know when someone, especially your boyfriend, is giving you complete edge. Like last week, before the break, he was like, &quot;Oh, I can&#039;t wait to see you, I miss you...bla bla bla,&quot; now all I get is a, &quot;Sure, why not.&quot; I&#039;m not asking him to give up the game for me, I&#039;m not asking for his complete attention. All I&#039;m asking for is at least a good five minutes. Is that so wrong? Just a little respect and consideration. Last friday, I was there for two hours and I literally spent more time with his mother because he had a &quot;quest&quot; to complete.  I was telling him this, and I noticed he wasn&#039;t listening, and I asked if he was. He replied, &quot; I am, but what you&#039;re telling me is unimportant.&quot; I was shocked. I said, &quot;So, you think that everything I&#039;m telling you is unimportant?&quot; and he said, &quot;Well yeah.&quot; I was literally going to cry, and lots of people think I should have slapped him, but we were on the phone so I couldn&#039;t.  I&#039;m usually quite talkative, as in I like a good conversation, but I was growing quiet, which is what I do when I&#039;m upset, and he asked me, &quot;Are you going to say anything,&quot; I said, &quot;What do you want me to say?&quot; He said, &quot;I don&#039;t know, but if you&#039;re not going to say anything, then you are wasting my time.&quot; I was completely floored. Shattered if you will. I asked, &quot; So are you saying I&#039;m a waste of time?&quot; to which he bluntly said, &quot;Well, if you&#039;re not going to say anything, then yeah you are. I&#039;m busy playing and you&#039;re just wasting my time and it&#039;s pissing me off.&quot; I&#039;m not one to cry often, but that did it. I cried. That was one of the most hurtful things that anyone has ever said to me. I mean, I&#039;ve had worse, but....Holy shit. Pardon my language, but, is this what becomes of those who become addicted to this game? I had no idea that it was &quot;wrong&quot; for a concerned girlfriend to ask for just a few minutes of her boyfriend&#039;s time. Anyways, my mom found out, she somehow involved herself and was yelling, but I told her to go away. I&#039;m a teenager so, yeah, you know how it is. She later said I was wasting phone and life time for this arguement, which of course just frustrated me even more.  Then I ended up being late for school this morning, and she yelled at me saying I was stupid for arguing, and I was just being pitiful. I&#039;m barely ever late, I&#039;m actually quite early. Then I called her after school telling her I was going to Paul&#039;s house and she wouldn&#039;t let me simply because she thought he was &quot;crap&quot;. I didn&#039;t do anything wrong, and I was being punished for a mere arguement that was no concern of hers.  I told Paul, and he simply brushed it off his shoulders, told me to call him later, and hung up.  No goodbye, nothing.  Later on msn, he asked, &quot;So I guess I&#039;m not seeing you for a while huh?&quot; and I said, &quot;Maybe not. But think of it this way, more playing time for you.&quot; He didn&#039;t note my sarcasm and replied, &quot;That&#039;s right! Oh man! That&#039;s great!&quot; My boyfriend is falling for this game and he&#039;s bringing our relationship with him. I don&#039;t hate the game, I just hate what it&#039;s doing to someone I care about.  You may critisize me, saying I&#039;m just a miniscule little teenager, what the hell do I know. She&#039;s only 16, she &quot;haven&#039;t seen the world yet&quot;. Well, I&#039;ve seen enough of this world. And if all it has to offer is warcraft and a boyfriend that will say those things to me, when a week ago they were things he wouldn&#039;t dare say, then I think this world needs to be remade. I think there needs to be a limit.  But hey, what do I know?]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well,  I don&#8217;t know what to say to any of this because I&#8217;m only 16.  I have a boyfriend who is completely drowning in world of warcraft, and I don&#8217;t really care that he wants to play, or whatever.  It&#8217;s his choice.  But what pisses me off is that he won&#8217;t give me a few minutes to say &#8220;Hi, how are you?&#8221; Instead, like he did on friday, he opens the door and runs back so he can finish his game and mind you, he lives in a building. I was made to walk 3 flights by myself in a place I&#8217;ve only been to three times in my life. Last night, I wanted to talk to him about being a little rude lately, and I wanted to ask him to lay off a bit, to which he laughed and didn&#8217;t take me seriously. He thought I was being accusatory and I was wrongfully accusing him of things he didn&#8217;t do. Believe me, and I think all girls will agree, but you just know when someone, especially your boyfriend, is giving you complete edge. Like last week, before the break, he was like, &#8220;Oh, I can&#8217;t wait to see you, I miss you&#8230;bla bla bla,&#8221; now all I get is a, &#8220;Sure, why not.&#8221; I&#8217;m not asking him to give up the game for me, I&#8217;m not asking for his complete attention. All I&#8217;m asking for is at least a good five minutes. Is that so wrong? Just a little respect and consideration. Last friday, I was there for two hours and I literally spent more time with his mother because he had a &#8220;quest&#8221; to complete.  I was telling him this, and I noticed he wasn&#8217;t listening, and I asked if he was. He replied, &#8221; I am, but what you&#8217;re telling me is unimportant.&#8221; I was shocked. I said, &#8220;So, you think that everything I&#8217;m telling you is unimportant?&#8221; and he said, &#8220;Well yeah.&#8221; I was literally going to cry, and lots of people think I should have slapped him, but we were on the phone so I couldn&#8217;t.  I&#8217;m usually quite talkative, as in I like a good conversation, but I was growing quiet, which is what I do when I&#8217;m upset, and he asked me, &#8220;Are you going to say anything,&#8221; I said, &#8220;What do you want me to say?&#8221; He said, &#8220;I don&#8217;t know, but if you&#8217;re not going to say anything, then you are wasting my time.&#8221; I was completely floored. Shattered if you will. I asked, &#8221; So are you saying I&#8217;m a waste of time?&#8221; to which he bluntly said, &#8220;Well, if you&#8217;re not going to say anything, then yeah you are. I&#8217;m busy playing and you&#8217;re just wasting my time and it&#8217;s pissing me off.&#8221; I&#8217;m not one to cry often, but that did it. I cried. That was one of the most hurtful things that anyone has ever said to me. I mean, I&#8217;ve had worse, but&#8230;.Holy shit. Pardon my language, but, is this what becomes of those who become addicted to this game? I had no idea that it was &#8220;wrong&#8221; for a concerned girlfriend to ask for just a few minutes of her boyfriend&#8217;s time. Anyways, my mom found out, she somehow involved herself and was yelling, but I told her to go away. I&#8217;m a teenager so, yeah, you know how it is. She later said I was wasting phone and life time for this arguement, which of course just frustrated me even more.  Then I ended up being late for school this morning, and she yelled at me saying I was stupid for arguing, and I was just being pitiful. I&#8217;m barely ever late, I&#8217;m actually quite early. Then I called her after school telling her I was going to Paul&#8217;s house and she wouldn&#8217;t let me simply because she thought he was &#8220;crap&#8221;. I didn&#8217;t do anything wrong, and I was being punished for a mere arguement that was no concern of hers.  I told Paul, and he simply brushed it off his shoulders, told me to call him later, and hung up.  No goodbye, nothing.  Later on msn, he asked, &#8220;So I guess I&#8217;m not seeing you for a while huh?&#8221; and I said, &#8220;Maybe not. But think of it this way, more playing time for you.&#8221; He didn&#8217;t note my sarcasm and replied, &#8220;That&#8217;s right! Oh man! That&#8217;s great!&#8221; My boyfriend is falling for this game and he&#8217;s bringing our relationship with him. I don&#8217;t hate the game, I just hate what it&#8217;s doing to someone I care about.  You may critisize me, saying I&#8217;m just a miniscule little teenager, what the hell do I know. She&#8217;s only 16, she &#8220;haven&#8217;t seen the world yet&#8221;. Well, I&#8217;ve seen enough of this world. And if all it has to offer is warcraft and a boyfriend that will say those things to me, when a week ago they were things he wouldn&#8217;t dare say, then I think this world needs to be remade. I think there needs to be a limit.  But hey, what do I know?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Another Kate				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16464</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Another Kate]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 21:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16464</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[LOL at nagging wife.  Most of my posts are not just about my life but about other&#039;s stories.  
He wants to sit and play wow, you want to sit and play wow? great, good for you, I happen to like to go and and &quot;fool&quot; with the real world.  

And I don&#039;t consider the 2 minutes it takes yo reply to a post before work as &quot;spending all my time on here&quot;.  I check the news, read a few forums and thats about it.  The rest of the time I spend at work, with my kids and with my family.  You know, important stuff.

Great that foreplay to you is a few key strokes while your partner kills a Boss, I prefer a real kiss compared to /kiss.  Go figure.

I even play wow *shock* but not to the detriment of my family.  I am not anti-wow,  I have a family and to me that should always come first.  I would find it hard for anyone in their right mind to disagree that kids should wait until you finish a raid before you get them dinner or spend time with them.

But that&#039;s what some gamers do.  It&#039;s not just their &quot;nagging&quot; partners that they are ignoring, but the children that they chose to bring into this world.  One woman had DSS on her doorstep because she left her husband in charge of the 2 yr old why she went shopping and when she got home the cops were there as the Dad was too busy playing wow he didn&#039;t notice HIS child open the front door and go onto the road.

This isn&#039;t all about &quot;me, me, me&quot; we as parents are responsible for our kids.  Maybe when you have some you will know this.  Or if you do, you may have it more under control.  But not everyone is like you.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LOL at nagging wife.  Most of my posts are not just about my life but about other&#8217;s stories.<br />
He wants to sit and play wow, you want to sit and play wow? great, good for you, I happen to like to go and and &#8220;fool&#8221; with the real world.  </p>
<p>And I don&#8217;t consider the 2 minutes it takes yo reply to a post before work as &#8220;spending all my time on here&#8221;.  I check the news, read a few forums and thats about it.  The rest of the time I spend at work, with my kids and with my family.  You know, important stuff.</p>
<p>Great that foreplay to you is a few key strokes while your partner kills a Boss, I prefer a real kiss compared to /kiss.  Go figure.</p>
<p>I even play wow *shock* but not to the detriment of my family.  I am not anti-wow,  I have a family and to me that should always come first.  I would find it hard for anyone in their right mind to disagree that kids should wait until you finish a raid before you get them dinner or spend time with them.</p>
<p>But that&#8217;s what some gamers do.  It&#8217;s not just their &#8220;nagging&#8221; partners that they are ignoring, but the children that they chose to bring into this world.  One woman had DSS on her doorstep because she left her husband in charge of the 2 yr old why she went shopping and when she got home the cops were there as the Dad was too busy playing wow he didn&#8217;t notice HIS child open the front door and go onto the road.</p>
<p>This isn&#8217;t all about &#8220;me, me, me&#8221; we as parents are responsible for our kids.  Maybe when you have some you will know this.  Or if you do, you may have it more under control.  But not everyone is like you.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: wowchic				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16443</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wowchic]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 14:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16443</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Why is &quot;another kate&quot; always on here? &quot;Another kate&quot;, I am a wife and I love WOW! Shut up with your tacky &quot;feel sorry for me&quot; inputs. I come on this site to read other info about the game and from time to time, I come to this blah blah forum and read what is up with the latest boohoos and I always see you. Maybe if you werent so busy on the internet pouring out your whiney butt comments then maybe your man or whatever would not have got busy fingering the keyboard and maybe fingering you. My husband and I play together and its awesome couple time and the foreplay is so much fun as well. We pst. each other with I think your sexy and hey baby come do me messages and trust me our bed sees much action. 
  For everyone else that complains, like I have said before. Shut up..its just a game and understand there are some people, knowing I am one, that dont like to get out and fool with the rest of the stupid world. Rather get up go to work, come home kiss myhusband and enjoy a good dungeon or a few quest. Give my man some love and go to bed.  Does the &quot;other&quot; person in your life HAVE to be sitting next to you at all times? GET A  LIFE!!! I am not a big holy roller but if any of you are &quot;christians&quot; then read proverbs about a nagging wife. 

-A Nagging wife is like a drippy faucett!!!]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why is &#8220;another kate&#8221; always on here? &#8220;Another kate&#8221;, I am a wife and I love WOW! Shut up with your tacky &#8220;feel sorry for me&#8221; inputs. I come on this site to read other info about the game and from time to time, I come to this blah blah forum and read what is up with the latest boohoos and I always see you. Maybe if you werent so busy on the internet pouring out your whiney butt comments then maybe your man or whatever would not have got busy fingering the keyboard and maybe fingering you. My husband and I play together and its awesome couple time and the foreplay is so much fun as well. We pst. each other with I think your sexy and hey baby come do me messages and trust me our bed sees much action.<br />
  For everyone else that complains, like I have said before. Shut up..its just a game and understand there are some people, knowing I am one, that dont like to get out and fool with the rest of the stupid world. Rather get up go to work, come home kiss myhusband and enjoy a good dungeon or a few quest. Give my man some love and go to bed.  Does the &#8220;other&#8221; person in your life HAVE to be sitting next to you at all times? GET A  LIFE!!! I am not a big holy roller but if any of you are &#8220;christians&#8221; then read proverbs about a nagging wife. </p>
<p>-A Nagging wife is like a drippy faucett!!!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Another Kate				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16424</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Another Kate]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 08:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16424</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Where did I say I &quot;liked&quot; little boys?  Learn to read complete sentences not just words.

I called YOU a little boy :) and &quot;like&quot; has nothing to do with THAT!]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Where did I say I &#8220;liked&#8221; little boys?  Learn to read complete sentences not just words.</p>
<p>I called YOU a little boy 🙂 and &#8220;like&#8221; has nothing to do with THAT!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: LMAO				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16406</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[LMAO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2007 22:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16406</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[LMAO if you liking little boys &quot;Another Kate&quot; you should not really be here, but then again who am i to criticise your desires like you do others LMAO :)]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LMAO if you liking little boys &#8220;Another Kate&#8221; you should not really be here, but then again who am i to criticise your desires like you do others LMAO 🙂</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Another Kate				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16404</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Another Kate]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2007 21:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16404</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Ok, couple of points, 1. yes I am aware that some, not all gaming is done on the internet.  Your point about that being? switch it off?  My kid is in final yr of high school and kinda needs it at the moment.
2. Um, WIDOW used as term of a spouse that has died came before the spider, thats where the spiders got the name from.  And how do you know they are self-righteous? The male spider may have pissed her off? She may have PMS? Doesn&#039;t really matter, she wins :)
3. WE are living in the REAL world.  It is the addicted gamer that chooses to live in fantasyland.
4.LOL the gamer would get more sucking if they got off the computer and showered more!
5. yes I agree with this last statement.
6. Anymore holes that you would like me to pick in your arguement little boy?]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ok, couple of points, 1. yes I am aware that some, not all gaming is done on the internet.  Your point about that being? switch it off?  My kid is in final yr of high school and kinda needs it at the moment.<br />
2. Um, WIDOW used as term of a spouse that has died came before the spider, thats where the spiders got the name from.  And how do you know they are self-righteous? The male spider may have pissed her off? She may have PMS? Doesn&#8217;t really matter, she wins 🙂<br />
3. WE are living in the REAL world.  It is the addicted gamer that chooses to live in fantasyland.<br />
4.LOL the gamer would get more sucking if they got off the computer and showered more!<br />
5. yes I agree with this last statement.<br />
6. Anymore holes that you would like me to pick in your arguement little boy?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: RL Guy needs help				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16403</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[RL Guy needs help]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2007 21:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16403</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Just wanted to leave a note that women are not the only victims here. But, I can completely relate to them. I have two children, an 8 year old and 10 month old. My wife because consumed with L2 when I was bored of playing after 1 month. Not knowing how deeply addicted she was,  I let her have her freedom to play. Something she would dramatically insist on having. HER FREEDOM TO PLAY. Little did I know that she was chatting out of game and even having cybersex with some of the damn geek boys! This was her &quot;safe&quot; cheating as they weren&#039;t in person. As if any phone sex would be forgiveable as well... I would often comment on the flirtation and insist that she not get wrapped up in these trivial relationships. Stupid ass me since she had already escalated to cheating. I let her talk me into getting WOW and she had boyfriends that followed. WTF! I should have cut it off, but all I could do was beg that she pay attention to our infant child and not yell at our 8 year old daughter. Forget the lack of her participation in my life or our home... Then she lashed out at me, saying I was to blame for her unhappiness. THAT I WAS A TYRANT AT HOME DEMANDING HER TO DO MY WILL.... Believe me, I have been nothing, but patient and look what it got me. I even believed her a little that maybe I did do something wrong, that I was to blame and did not deserve to live! DON&#039;T LET THEM CONVINCE YOU!! YOU ARE NOT DOING ANYTHING WRONG EXCEPT TRYING TO FIND A WAY TO WAKE THEM UP!!  I&#039;m afraid that divorce may be inevitable, but I care too much to give up now... She has deleted her game and all the elements that have come with the addiction! I have gotten her to delete her MySpace, IM, WOW, L2 and webmail accounts... I hope I can forgive her for her infidelity!!! Having a stable and happy family is so important, that I need to find a way to forgive and forget, but somehow not loose myself in doing that! I can&#039;t deal with the pain forever, so how do I extinguish the anger and disgust I am suppressing inside???? There is so much to say, but this forum is already so long...]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just wanted to leave a note that women are not the only victims here. But, I can completely relate to them. I have two children, an 8 year old and 10 month old. My wife because consumed with L2 when I was bored of playing after 1 month. Not knowing how deeply addicted she was,  I let her have her freedom to play. Something she would dramatically insist on having. HER FREEDOM TO PLAY. Little did I know that she was chatting out of game and even having cybersex with some of the damn geek boys! This was her &#8220;safe&#8221; cheating as they weren&#8217;t in person. As if any phone sex would be forgiveable as well&#8230; I would often comment on the flirtation and insist that she not get wrapped up in these trivial relationships. Stupid ass me since she had already escalated to cheating. I let her talk me into getting WOW and she had boyfriends that followed. WTF! I should have cut it off, but all I could do was beg that she pay attention to our infant child and not yell at our 8 year old daughter. Forget the lack of her participation in my life or our home&#8230; Then she lashed out at me, saying I was to blame for her unhappiness. THAT I WAS A TYRANT AT HOME DEMANDING HER TO DO MY WILL&#8230;. Believe me, I have been nothing, but patient and look what it got me. I even believed her a little that maybe I did do something wrong, that I was to blame and did not deserve to live! DON&#8217;T LET THEM CONVINCE YOU!! YOU ARE NOT DOING ANYTHING WRONG EXCEPT TRYING TO FIND A WAY TO WAKE THEM UP!!  I&#8217;m afraid that divorce may be inevitable, but I care too much to give up now&#8230; She has deleted her game and all the elements that have come with the addiction! I have gotten her to delete her MySpace, IM, WOW, L2 and webmail accounts&#8230; I hope I can forgive her for her infidelity!!! Having a stable and happy family is so important, that I need to find a way to forgive and forget, but somehow not loose myself in doing that! I can&#8217;t deal with the pain forever, so how do I extinguish the anger and disgust I am suppressing inside???? There is so much to say, but this forum is already so long&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: LMAO				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/comment-page-7/#comment-16402</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[LMAO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2007 19:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/09/21/warcraft-widows/#comment-16402</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[LMAO man I just can&#039;t contain my laughter at you fucking contraDICKting shity hormonal freaks, like you&#039;re moaning and whining about your fucking men spending all their time playing wow or what ever game you want to moan about, shitting hell you D- retards, you do realise that this gaming is done on the internet don&#039;t ya??? Hell no of course you don&#039;t, how could you with your own heads so far up your arses you see the moon with teeth around it, talk about reality, the real world, pull your heads out once in a while, wash your own righteous shit from your eyes and god damn hair and then take a real good look around you, oh yea, and while you&#039;re at it, have a think where another term for &quot;WIDOW&quot; comes from, could it be anything to do with the &quot;BLACK WIDOW SPIDER&quot; the self-righteous arachnid that kills off it&#039;s spouse once it&#039;s had what it needs from him, shit, you calling them addicts and nerds, what the fuck you all think you&#039;re doing here posting! man if only you women were as good at sucking your men as you are at posting, then maybe you&#039;d not be single and looking for &quot;Mind Loooooove&quot; and sympathy. Geeeeeeez
But also Widows of wow, beware, be very aware as there is a new arachnid amongst you, prowling this forum for his prey, yes I said a he and his transparency is so obvious should you wipe your self pitiful tears from your mind, but don&#039;t worry for the Son of God is here to save you all, kneel God damn it and bow before the Oracle of all relational problems, be praised LMAO 
PS, yea man, contadickting was miss-spelt on purpose, for those of you who might think I&#039;m from outer Mongolia just to appease your instability. Thank you for the laughs by the way :)  
And no, I don&#039;t play wow, I just know women are as fucked up as men, rock on dudetts.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LMAO man I just can&#8217;t contain my laughter at you fucking contraDICKting shity hormonal freaks, like you&#8217;re moaning and whining about your fucking men spending all their time playing wow or what ever game you want to moan about, shitting hell you D- retards, you do realise that this gaming is done on the internet don&#8217;t ya??? Hell no of course you don&#8217;t, how could you with your own heads so far up your arses you see the moon with teeth around it, talk about reality, the real world, pull your heads out once in a while, wash your own righteous shit from your eyes and god damn hair and then take a real good look around you, oh yea, and while you&#8217;re at it, have a think where another term for &#8220;WIDOW&#8221; comes from, could it be anything to do with the &#8220;BLACK WIDOW SPIDER&#8221; the self-righteous arachnid that kills off it&#8217;s spouse once it&#8217;s had what it needs from him, shit, you calling them addicts and nerds, what the fuck you all think you&#8217;re doing here posting! man if only you women were as good at sucking your men as you are at posting, then maybe you&#8217;d not be single and looking for &#8220;Mind Loooooove&#8221; and sympathy. Geeeeeeez<br />
But also Widows of wow, beware, be very aware as there is a new arachnid amongst you, prowling this forum for his prey, yes I said a he and his transparency is so obvious should you wipe your self pitiful tears from your mind, but don&#8217;t worry for the Son of God is here to save you all, kneel God damn it and bow before the Oracle of all relational problems, be praised LMAO<br />
PS, yea man, contadickting was miss-spelt on purpose, for those of you who might think I&#8217;m from outer Mongolia just to appease your instability. Thank you for the laughs by the way 🙂<br />
And no, I don&#8217;t play wow, I just know women are as fucked up as men, rock on dudetts.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
			</channel>
</rss>
