<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Loly	</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/01/10/loly/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/01/10/loly/</link>
	<description>Hello.  I see you.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Tue, 28 Feb 2017 12:33:23 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.1</generator>
			<item>
				<title>
				By: Why we can&#8217;t have nice things. &#171; Broken Toys				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/01/10/loly/comment-page-1/#comment-50197</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Why we can&#8217;t have nice things. &#171; Broken Toys]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 23:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/01/10/loly/#comment-50197</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[[...] but police work. But at the same time, the longer a known farmer is sitting on a server being mocked by the player base, the longer the broken window corrupts its environment. At the same time, an aggressive assault on [...]]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[&#8230;] but police work. But at the same time, the longer a known farmer is sitting on a server being mocked by the player base, the longer the broken window corrupts its environment. At the same time, an aggressive assault on [&#8230;]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: Broken Toys » Blog Archive » Why we can’t have nice things.				</title>
				<link>https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/01/10/loly/comment-page-1/#comment-2255</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Broken Toys » Blog Archive » Why we can’t have nice things.]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2005 11:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afkgamer.github.io/afkgamer-com/archives/2005/01/10/loly/#comment-2255</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[[...] Second - enforcement is the first, and impossible, line of defense. You cannot rely solely on enforcement to solve the problem. Sheer mathematics is working against you - there are more farmers than you have support staff, assuming your support staff ignores the rest of the game and does nothing but police work. But at the same time, the longer a known farmer is sitting on a server being mocked by the player base, the longer the broken window corrupts its environment. At the same time, an aggressive assault on farmers will hit the innocent as well -because farmers, after all, are nothing but players who have honed discovering the risk-reward breakdown to its razor&#039;s edge. And every one you remove from the game will be replaced by four more. Thus why it is impossible. And necessary. No one said running an online game was easy. [...]]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[&#8230;] Second &#8211; enforcement is the first, and impossible, line of defense. You cannot rely solely on enforcement to solve the problem. Sheer mathematics is working against you &#8211; there are more farmers than you have support staff, assuming your support staff ignores the rest of the game and does nothing but police work. But at the same time, the longer a known farmer is sitting on a server being mocked by the player base, the longer the broken window corrupts its environment. At the same time, an aggressive assault on farmers will hit the innocent as well -because farmers, after all, are nothing but players who have honed discovering the risk-reward breakdown to its razor&#8217;s edge. And every one you remove from the game will be replaced by four more. Thus why it is impossible. And necessary. No one said running an online game was easy. [&#8230;]</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
			</channel>
</rss>
